<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Western Australia on Nii&#39;s Travel Blog</title>
    <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/tags/western-australia/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Western Australia on Nii&#39;s Travel Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2016 20:40:11 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://travel.niiteki.io/tags/western-australia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Perth</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/perth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2016 20:40:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/perth/</guid>
      <description>And so ends our long loooong trek back.
Kudos to Steph for driving for what I think was 5 hours in total today!
We left Kalbarri in the morning and went to &amp;ldquo;Barbara&amp;rsquo;s Bake House&amp;rdquo;, which was someone&amp;rsquo;s house with a van that drives around delivering pastries! Turns out they started their first day off in three weeks today. So no pastries for us :(
We continued onward to Perth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kalbarri</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/kalbarri/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2016 20:40:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/kalbarri/</guid>
      <description>We got up super early today, at 730am. This was so we actually see the dolphins this time around.
Steph thinks it was lame, because it was really windy and cold, it was raining, and the dolphins their sweet time to say hello.
We also didn&amp;rsquo;t get a chance to feed them! The volunteer yesterday gave us a tip to wear &amp;ldquo;outlandish clothing&amp;rdquo; so that we are distinct enough so that we get chosen during the feeding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monkey Mia Second Day</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/monkeymia2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2016 20:40:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/monkeymia2/</guid>
      <description>So this is the second day at Monkey Mia.
We actually didn&amp;rsquo;t do anything noteworthy.
Our itinerary for today.
 Sleep in Watch some TV (Zootopia!) Buy some water (we&amp;rsquo;ve had to ration our water since last night because we ran out) See what the dolphins were up to (we missed them!) Eat some instant noodles (with an egg of course) Watch some K-Drama (W is SO good) Nap Write this blogpost while sitting on a bench outside  So far so good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monkey Mia First Day</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/monkeymia1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2016 20:40:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/monkeymia1/</guid>
      <description>Today is the first day of major MAJOR driving.
We gotta make it all the way back to Perth somehow! So we decided to stop at different points, but this includes a little bit more driving. A &amp;lsquo;little&amp;rsquo; to some people might be 1.5 hours extra or so, but like a friend of mine said, when you&amp;rsquo;ve driven all the way to Exmouth, an extra 1.5 hours in the car can feel really, really long indeed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coral bay</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/coral-bay/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 20:40:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/coral-bay/</guid>
      <description>So today is the most vigorous and adventurous thing we&amp;rsquo;ve done together since ever!
The Driving of Car We drove down from Exmouth in the morning. It was around 1 hour 45 minutes.
The Explorer of Sub Sea We were too early to check into the hostel so we went straight to the tour that we booked earlier. Its called Sub Sea Explorer and it involves snorkelling and a glass bottomed boat!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exmouth Second Day</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/exmouth2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2016 20:40:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/exmouth2/</guid>
      <description>So today was the first tour of the trip. We were looking forward to it, mostly because we travelled three days to get to this point!
We got picked up late from the bus stop at 11am instead of 1030am. Got a tour around Exmouth and learnt about the history of the area.
Here we have the lookout point of a now defunct lighthouse.
We went for a swim at Osprey Bay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exmouth</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/exmouth/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 20:40:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/exmouth/</guid>
      <description>Oh god we&amp;rsquo;re finally here!
I can&amp;rsquo;t believe we made it!
Departure We went to Bubinga Island in Carnarvon. Apparently its an island, but the river between is completely gone now. Sooo is it still an island? Who knows&amp;hellip;
Okay fine there was a little bit of water
We ate food on Bubinga Island-thing. Standard tasty cafe food.
There&amp;rsquo;s a water tower lookout that I went up.
Much civilisation!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carnarvon</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/carnarvon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2016 18:57:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/carnarvon/</guid>
      <description>So we continued on our extremely long journey to Exmouth.
Today we went to Carnarvon. I say &amp;lsquo;went&amp;rsquo;, but it was more of a long, arduous, challenging trek.
Yet here we are!
Oh god water! Oh wait that&amp;rsquo;s just a mirage
HELLO CIVILISATION! Me trying to take a selfie while Steph is constantly being eaten by flies
We stopped by the Billabong Roadhouse halfway. Steph drove the first half (good jerb!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geraldton</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/geraldton/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2016 18:57:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/geraldton/</guid>
      <description>For some mysterious reason we decided to drive all the way to Exmouth. The place is allegedly great for snorkelling, swimming, beach activities among other things that we never ever do or have interest in.
Yanchep Starting from Currambine the night before, we drove to Yanchep to get some tasty foods.
We visited Yanchep National park. We missed out on the last two tickets for the Crystal Caves guided tour so we visited the super short collapsed cave walk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Albany</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/albany/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2016 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/albany/</guid>
      <description>Albany For some mysterious reason we decided to go to Albany this long weekend. It was a short holiday I suppose, and it was too expensive to go and fly somewhere for such a short period of time. Plus I haven&amp;rsquo;t been to Albany!
The trip Non-stop it would be a 4.5 hour drive to Albany. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t SOUND horrific. But in the last couple of hours you start to derp really hard.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>