<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hong Kong on Nii&#39;s Travel Blog</title>
    <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/tags/hong-kong/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hong Kong on Nii&#39;s Travel Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2015 19:25:11 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://travel.niiteki.io/tags/hong-kong/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Mk III Part Three - Other Stuff</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/hong-kong-mk-iii-part-three-other-stuff/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2015 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/hong-kong-mk-iii-part-three-other-stuff/</guid>
      <description>Tech stuff I love Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s airport express train&amp;rsquo;s progress bar.
One of the malls had seating areas which exist only to charge your phone. Its a great idea! Too bad my phone&amp;rsquo;s battery capacity is too big now, so these are useless to me.
Neat shops Ghibli Shop! Ghibli shops are great! The studio doesn&amp;rsquo;t make movies anymore (I think?) so its nice to see that the knick knacks are still being sold.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Mk III Part Two - Food</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/hong-kong-mk-iii-part-two-food/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2015 01:27:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/hong-kong-mk-iii-part-two-food/</guid>
      <description>This won&amp;rsquo;t be a daily blog, mostly because life in Hong Kong tends to blur into a big mush of stuff. So here are some highlights.
Food in Hong Kong! Service The workers here work at a breakneck pace, and I find myself constantly slowing everyone down. Its a lovely change from Malaysia. Here in Hong Kong, the service is bad because there are a billion people and so much to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Mk III Part One - Arrival and Accomodation</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/hong-kong-mk-iii-part-one-arrival-and-accomodation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2015 17:35:35 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/hong-kong-mk-iii-part-one-arrival-and-accomodation/</guid>
      <description>Hello again! Here we are in Hong Kong yet again. This is our third time here! I guess we never learn. Who would&amp;rsquo;ve thought that Hong Kong is not the most ideal place to relax and chill out.
Anyway might as well track our progress. When I&amp;rsquo;m 100 years old I&amp;rsquo;ll be saying wise words such as:
 Damn son, I was in Hong Kong 3 times by the time I was your age.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>