<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Japan on Nii&#39;s Travel Blog</title>
    <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/tags/japan/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Japan on Nii&#39;s Travel Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2015 23:07:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://travel.niiteki.io/tags/japan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Japan-Korea Day 6 - Miyajima 2</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan-korea-day-6-miyajima-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2015 23:07:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan-korea-day-6-miyajima-2/</guid>
      <description>Miyajima Day 2 Damn today was extremely hot and humid. I felt like I was having a bath, except with clothes on and while standing. The overly accommodating but creepy Minshuku owner gave us paper fans, which was probably the most useful equipment that we&amp;rsquo;ve had this entire trip.
It was nice to have a change of scenery from the city, although it was only for two days. By the end of the day, we were looking forwards to returning back to civilisation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japan-Korea Day 5 - Miyajima</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan-korea-day-5-miyajima/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2015 23:01:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan-korea-day-5-miyajima/</guid>
      <description>Miyajima Ok here we go. Itsukushima island (yes I know I just said Itsuku-island Island).
The home of the killer deer apparently. They will go through your bags and stuff. I better bring a baseball bat&amp;hellip;
Oh. Never mind.
This is all future tense of course. We&amp;rsquo;re currently on a rocket ship on rails known as the Shinkansen!
I always get a kick out of going in one. This is the first time I&amp;rsquo;ve been on the Nozomi, which is the express Shinkansen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japan-Korea Day 4 - Kobe</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan-korea-day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 21:05:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan-korea-day-4/</guid>
      <description>Homestay Masterchef Steph learnt to cook some tamagoyaki today! The host mother was happy to teach.
I think it turned out okay, it tasted good. But then again, eggs are always da best!
Those mini sausages were also very tasty! 
Kobe City Today we decided to go ahead and explore the city in Kobe. It was HOT! Not hot hot, but sticky, humid hot. We don&amp;rsquo;t know why everyone was complaining that yesterday was hot, when it was miserable, raining and cool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japan-Korea Day 3 - Himeji Castle</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan-korea-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2015 21:03:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan-korea-day-3/</guid>
      <description>First day in Kobe &amp;hellip;which didn&amp;rsquo;t actually have anything to do with Kobe 
Step 1. Find some suitable clothing It has been overcast and raining pretty much non-stop since we got here. This was never the plan really, as Steph only packed 8kg full of short shorts, tank-tops, and thin blouses. Everyone else in Himeji is walking around in jeans, jackets, raincoats and boots, so she felt really out of place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japan-Korea Day 2 - 奈良 の鹿</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan-korea-day-2-nai-liang-nolu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2015 21:02:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan-korea-day-2-nai-liang-nolu/</guid>
      <description>Deer-land! Deer everyone,
Today we went to Nara Park! Oh deer-ie me. I think I should stop with these lame puns or you, my precious reader, will decide to stop reading.
And we all know this blog needs more hits. I get like, one hit per year (hi Mum!).
I discovered an electric vehicle quick charging station!
I was scared to use this tap at the guesthouse. Who knows what each of those million dials could do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japan-Korea Day 1 - Nara</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2015 17:53:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan/</guid>
      <description>Nara! 奈良市! Big Temples and Stuff! Hello! We&amp;rsquo;ve finally landed in Japan. We&amp;rsquo;ve been to this country way too many times yet here we are! I think its because we&amp;rsquo;ve reached the point where going to Japan is just a comfortable process. We speak the language (terribly), and we can blend in (terribly)!
We took Malaysia Airlines this time to the country. The flights were cheaper and quite empty. I assume its because of the recent issues Malaysia Airlines have been having regarding keeping track of their planes, but seriously the flight was pretty good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japan and Korea!</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan-and-korea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2015 10:48:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan-and-korea/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re heading to Japan and Korea next week! Exciting. Except for the fact that it&amp;rsquo;s going to rain like crazy for the entire time we are there, only to clear up into beautiful skies as soon as we leave.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tokyo 2014 Day 2</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/1840/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2014 11:45:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/1840/</guid>
      <description>Today we rode our bikes around. Tried to go to ryougoku by bike. Took ages but it was closed when we got there! Very disappointing, was looking forward to eat sumo food. Not so I can get fat(ter) or anything. Just that it’s one of those foods that people don’t know about. Maybe it tastes awful?
We then went to Shinjuku in the evening. Kabukicho had a pretty DODGY vibe to it so we didn’t stay long.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tokyo 2014 Day 1</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/tokyo-mk-3-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2014 17:40:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/tokyo-mk-3-day-1/</guid>
      <description>Aaand we are back in Japan. I suppose it was going to happen eventually.
This time around will be Tokyo, Kyoto and Osaka, but this time we will be adding Takayama to the list. Popular vacation town in the middle of the mountains somewhere. As luck would have it a volcano erupted there recently. Luckily the winds a blowing the ash in the other direction so we should be good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leaving for Kyoto</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/leaving-for-kyoto/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2008 09:56:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/leaving-for-kyoto/</guid>
      <description>Hi all,
We’re gonna be leaving for Kyoto later today. The place we’re staying at is kindof dodgy actually, its 40 minutes away from the city centre and has a curfew. Plus it looks like a giant complex of some sort. Its a youth hostel, rather than a backpackers hostel so I don’t really know what to expect. Utano Youth Hostel link. Packing up now. Seeyou soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Osaka 3</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/osaka-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2008 10:19:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/osaka-3/</guid>
      <description>Good morning! Its our last day in Osaka. We’ll be going to Tenshinsuji or something. At 2.6km, its the biggest shopping arcade in the world apparently. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Osaka 2</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/osaka-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2008 18:40:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/osaka-2/</guid>
      <description>Greetings all! Nice to have wifi at Osaka. We went out today, only 3 of us because the others were too busy sleeping. I managed to buy some clothes (!). I got a jacket thats waaay too small for me, so I’ll have to slim down when I get back from japan. I also got a sweet watch thats sortof transparent so you can see the innards. Also got some manga to practice Japanese with (Death Note, Trigun and Haruhi Suzumiya).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We made it in Osaka</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/we-made-it-in-osaka/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 22:10:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/we-made-it-in-osaka/</guid>
      <description>Ahh made it to Osaka. It was a 7 hour bus ride! The stupid driver kept accelerating and decelerating as well, so I’ve got really bad motion sickness. I really wanted to take the bullet train instead, but Alas and the others wanted to save money. On the way back to Tokyo I’ll probably take the bullet train, because that bus ride was awful.
Upon arriving, we got lost as usual.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leaving the biting cold behind me</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/leaving-the-biting-cold-behind-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 09:17:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/leaving-the-biting-cold-behind-me/</guid>
      <description>Hey all,
Sorry for the lack of updates. My laptop still has no wifi, and I’ll hopefully get it fixed soon. Hakuba trip is finished, snowboarding is great fun. I wish to do it again often. I’m going to leave in about 2 hours for Nagano, then taking the 7 hour bus to Osaka.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos from a few days ago</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/photos-from-a-few-days-ago/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2008 21:36:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/photos-from-a-few-days-ago/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been getting lazy uploading photos onto here, mostly because its such a poorly designed system. I’m disappointed in you Google! These photos are of our last few days in Tokyo. We went to Roppongi and Jump Festa. Roppongi was a really seedy red light district. There are lots of Nigerian hustlers on the streets (more annoying than the Mexican ones in Las Vegas actually). We went to a club called Gas Panic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snowboarding 2</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/snowboarding-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2008 20:18:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/snowboarding-2/</guid>
      <description>Completed another day of snowboarding. We were all meant to get up at 630am, but since we were all so tired from yesterday we ended up getting out of the house about 9 or 10am. Snowboarding was much more fun today, I managed to fall about 3&amp;frasl;4 as much as yesterday. I’ve also learnt to fall on different parts of my body, so by the end of the week my entire body should be manageable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snowboarding!</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/snowboarding/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2008 08:24:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/snowboarding/</guid>
      <description>Went snowboarding yesterday. Very humiliating, as I kept falling over. Also extremely painful for your wrist and tailbone. I couldn’t get up this morning becauase of how sore I was. But I am now awake and off to do it again. I should really take lessons, but I’m hoping all this youtube watching and forum reading will be enough =)
After 4 days of this stuff I should be pretty good I hope.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hakuba</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/hakuba/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2008 22:32:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/hakuba/</guid>
      <description>In Hakuba, Nagano. Skiing time. Will update more later, after I actually actually get to use the damn showers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asakusa</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/asakusa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2008 12:49:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/asakusa/</guid>
      <description>Melon bread! This stuff is really good. I’ve bought like 5 already. Its custard centre is rockmelon flavoured. The outer green bit is flavoured too!
Here are some photos of Asakusa. Its about 10 or 20 minutes walk from here. The giant senso-ji temple is here. They put raincoats on the mascots outside the building when it rains! The other day they put santa costumes on them too. Nice to know someone cares about them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Odaiba</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/odaiba/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2008 12:15:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/odaiba/</guid>
      <description>Went to Odaiba some on Tuesday. It was mostly the Museum of Innovation and Technology we wanted to check out. For the robots and cool stuff. But to our surprise, they decided to close on Tuesdays! So we decided to just head to Sega Joypolis instead. Its an indoor theme park of games and stuff. Pretty cool, but doesn’t beat a proper theme park.
Odaiba is an artificial island (similar to the one in Dubai), built by the Japanese government during the economic boom some decade or two ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Today</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2008 19:09:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/today/</guid>
      <description>Too lazy to get photos up today. Went to the senso-ji temple today. There was apparently a festival, using these badminton racquet things. Bought a DS USB charger and stylus so I can actually use my DS now! Prayed at a buddhist temple and got a fortune. It was perhaps the worst possible fortune ever. So I tied it on some stick thing so it will go away. Hope it does.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Akihabara again</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/akihabara-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2008 20:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/akihabara-again/</guid>
      <description>Ahh the life of a Japanese local. My personal space was violated! Crushed against a sea of people. Though I am quite impressed, the entire mob moves at a very very brisk pace. If this was in Australia someone in front will randomly stop and the crowd’s movement will be screwed up.
Shibuya at night! It was packed with people. All the shops were closed so I assume they were going to clubs or bars or something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japanese trains</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/japanese-trains/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2008 20:07:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/japanese-trains/</guid>
      <description>I’m really impressed with the Japanese train system. It goes absolutely EVERYWHERE! A lot of people that I know don’t even bother having cars, and just take the train everywhere. The cost is slightly higher than public transport usage in Perth, but you gotta pay for superiority.The main problem? The trains are so good, EVERYONE uses them. I took at train at peak hour to goto train at the Aunkai (an incredible martial art that requires another post on its own).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shibuya and Akihabara</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/shibuya-and-akihabara/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2008 14:04:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/shibuya-and-akihabara/</guid>
      <description>We returned to Akihabara again, since it was the most interesting place. This time, however, we split up into smaller groups. Was very fun. Got souvenirs and talked to some pre-war guy who is an ukiyo-e printer/artist now. I wanted to buy some paintings but the ones I wanted were about 1000 AUD.
Shibuya was insanely packed. We went to what is apparently the biggest crosswalk in the world! My youtube channel has some videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ginza, Aunkai, Ueno park and ueno zoo</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/ginza-aunkai-ueno-park-and-ueno-zoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2008 11:22:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/ginza-aunkai-ueno-park-and-ueno-zoo/</guid>
      <description>It hasn’t been that eventful for the past few days. Went to Ueno park and Ginza. We also went to an izakaya (Japanese bar), but we were told to go away. I’m assuming that they did not want foreigners but I’m really not sure. Interesting experience. Regardless, I managed to go to an izakaya the next night. More on that later.There are some pics of our visit to the zoo in this entry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ueno park</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/ueno-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2008 21:36:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/ueno-park/</guid>
      <description>After an hour of travelling on foot, we managed to reach the Ueno Park. Pretty cool. There was a buddhist shrine there!Here are some photos I took before we left. Cold and raining today. Chilling… This was taken from the rooftop of where I’m staying. A cemetary is so close by! A wall has been erected around the cemetary to scare people walking around it I suppose.
Not only that, here is a picture of the elevator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Akihabara photos</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/akihabara-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2008 11:03:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/akihabara-photos/</guid>
      <description>These are some photos when I visited Akihabara yesterday. Gotta love the train system here. Took almost no time to get there, and I assume its the same case for everywhere else. 11am. Friends still asleep. I think I’m going to kick them out of bed next time.
Apparently this car costs a million dollars. Not bad. Too scared to take a photo any closer in case the car’s owner has ninjas protecting it or something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Awake</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/awake/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2008 10:04:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/awake/</guid>
      <description>Been up for the past 3 hours. Jet lag is kind to me. The only problem is that my friends are still asleep and I’m waiting for them to wake up. Next time I’ll just leave on my own or something.
Just went to Akihabara yesterday. Its insanely cool. There’s tech everywhere!Currently drinking this awful green tea/water mix thing. It tastes just like water, but you get a green tea aftertaste.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arrived in Japan</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/arrived-in-japan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2008 22:41:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/arrived-in-japan/</guid>
      <description>Just arrived in Japan after a 12 hour flight. Good first impressions of Japan so far, insanely high density population and many many many train stops. Which is good… assuming you know where you’re going.
I’m in K’s Hostel at the moment. A very good place,., but this is the first hostel I’ve been to. Its like… Living with 50 other people. A weird experience, but not unwelcome. Good hostel though, its ranked the highest in Asia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos in Narita airport and LA</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/photos-in-narita-airport-and-la/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2008 18:16:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/photos-in-narita-airport-and-la/</guid>
      <description>Here are some photos I took initially.
…Real men take photos AFTER they finish their food.
First impressions in Japan? Interesting bathrooms (or lavatories, as the Americans call it). Every single toilet (well all the male ones as far as I know of course) have little baby seats, so you can stare at the baby while taking a dump I suppose.
Ahh an advanced toilet. What do these instructions lead to?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flight to Japan</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/flight-to-japan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2008 01:15:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/flight-to-japan/</guid>
      <description>On a plane with Victor, in the EXIT ROW!!! Quite spacy, with lots of leg room too. Hopefully for the next flight we’ll be on exit row as well, but I chose the squishy window seat instead, so I doubt I’ll get it.
Terrible night, hard to sleep. Had some red wine and scotch… on the rocks. Classy, but for someone with my nonexistent alcohol tolerance it overwhelms far too much.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First post</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/firstpp-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 21:37:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/firstpp-post/</guid>
      <description>Hello there!
This blog will hopefully chronicle my adventures into the Land of the Rising Sun, depending if I can be bothered to keep it updated. This is my first blog, so please tolerate any violations of blogging ettiquette =)
I will be in California for a week, then Tokyo, Kyoto, Hakuba and Osaka. I leave this Friday on the 28th of November at around 11pm. It’ll be a 10 hour flight to Tokyo, 7 hour rest (!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>