<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>California on Nii&#39;s Travel Blog</title>
    <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/tags/california/</link>
    <description>Recent content in California on Nii&#39;s Travel Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2008 10:47:00 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://travel.niiteki.io/tags/california/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood!</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/hollywood/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2008 10:47:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/hollywood/</guid>
      <description>[](/images/2010/10/dscf0075.jpg)
On our last day in USA, we dropped by Hollywood. It took a lot of trouble to get there, and the public transport was pretty scary at night. Hollywood remains underwhelming, mostly because we just came from Las Vegas (the place of overwhelming stuff).[
This is the La Quinta hotel at LAX. Nice hotel, though very pricy. They use neat USB sticks as keys to open the doors.
Hollywood! This is the Kodak Theatre, some fancy place that was closed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More photos of Las Vegas (daytime)</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/more-photos-of-las-vegas-daytime/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2008 10:39:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/more-photos-of-las-vegas-daytime/</guid>
      <description>Here are some more pics I took before I left. At the Flamingo hotel there is an exotic animals area such as pheasants and Australian black swans (!). Here’s a pheasant doing its thing.
Weirdly enough, there are flamingos at the flamingo hotel. Note their genetically awesome ability to stand on one leg.
A huge sphinx thing in front of Luxor hotel (which sports an egyptian theme).
The Luxor hotel from outside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going back</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/going-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2008 11:35:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/going-back/</guid>
      <description>Currently on the bus back to LA from Las Vegas. I have no idea how the internet works on a moving bus, but I’m assuming it is a satellite internet connection or something. Very cool bus this one… It even has power points and little tables (such as those seen in planes) in addition to the standard TV. 2 days in LA then we’re off to Japan!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anaheim, last day</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/anaheim-last-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2008 16:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/anaheim-last-day/</guid>
      <description>Cool trees! They remind me of Vice City or Miami or something. We should get those in Perth!
An American McDonalds meal. This is the BEST burger ever! It’s just a meat patty and lots and LOTS of mushrooms and mayonaisse. Just the way I like it.
California! And me with my tourist pose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disneyland part 2</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/disneyland-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2008 18:17:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/disneyland-part-2/</guid>
      <description>Just returned from Disneyland for the second day.Went to California Venture, the theme parks other half. It wasn’t as good but still had its moments. We went on almost every rollercoaster there, California Screamin’ being one of them. It was pretty cool! The sixth largest rollercoaster in the world I think. (2nd largest in the US, highest and longest upside portion in the world)
Watched the Disney show thing as well as went to the rides I couldn’t before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mornin’</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/mornin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2008 04:52:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/mornin/</guid>
      <description>Got up at 10am today. The other guys were sound asleep even at 11am. I kicked them awake and we should be heading off to sample an American McDonalds soon. We will then head to Califonia Venture, the ‘other’ Disneyland, which happens to be next door.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disneyland photos</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/disneyland-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2008 17:54:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/disneyland-photos/</guid>
      <description>Just came back from Disneyland. Legs hurt like hell after walking… not far at all. I suppose my legs still aren’t well made for walking around. Regardless it was better than I expected!
We dropped by the 7-11 convenience store on the way there. Beer is amazingly cheap!
…And sports drinks bottles are about 2x fatter than the ones in Australia. The Americans must need a lot of hydration.
Here are some random photos from Disneyland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Boy Blue Motel</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/little-boy-blue-motel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2008 06:38:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/little-boy-blue-motel/</guid>
      <description>Just arrived at LA and the motel we’ll be staying at for the next few days. Kinda old, but livable. What’s more annoying is the fact that the XD card reader is not working. I can’t pull pictures out! I’ll have to buy a new reader or something when I return to Japan. We’ll be here for two days and then head off to Las Vegas. Most of our time here will be spent going to Disneyland and maybe Hollywood if we can afford the exorbitant taxi fares.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flight to LA</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/flight-to-la/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2008 03:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/flight-to-la/</guid>
      <description>Currently on the plane to LA. American Airlines operates somewhat differently to Qantas but is still familiar enough I suppose.
We were in Japan for about 7 hours of lounging about. Upon entry my camera was detected in the metal detector. Normally I suppose this would be okay but here the Police can’t speak any English, and silently signal and wave you where to go, or tap you on the shoulder without a word.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First post</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/firstpp-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 21:37:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/firstpp-post/</guid>
      <description>Hello there!
This blog will hopefully chronicle my adventures into the Land of the Rising Sun, depending if I can be bothered to keep it updated. This is my first blog, so please tolerate any violations of blogging ettiquette =)
I will be in California for a week, then Tokyo, Kyoto, Hakuba and Osaka. I leave this Friday on the 28th of November at around 11pm. It’ll be a 10 hour flight to Tokyo, 7 hour rest (!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>