<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tech on Nii&#39;s Travel Blog</title>
    <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/tags/tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tech on Nii&#39;s Travel Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2015 17:51:31 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://travel.niiteki.io/tags/tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Migration to Hugo</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/migration-to-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2015 17:51:31 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/migration-to-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Again? I know, I know, I JUST migrated over to Ghost a few months ago. But no one really reads this anyway, so I don&amp;rsquo;t think I&amp;rsquo;m offending that many people.
Hugo is a Go based static site generator. Its really damn quick, and looks pretty good too! At first I thought Ghost would&amp;rsquo;ve been a good platform to work from.
But as it turns out, even though Ghost works really well, sorting out:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain Analytics with Cayley DB</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/blockchain-analytics-with-cayley-db/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2015 13:21:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/blockchain-analytics-with-cayley-db/</guid>
      <description>Bitcoin (and consequently, the Blockchain) have been making waves in the media over the past few years.
In this blog we will be covering the process of building relationships between blocks, transactions and addresses using Google&amp;rsquo;s Cayley DB. With this information we may be able to pinpoint important transfers of value and also build an ownership database on top of it to track high value individuals.
I&amp;rsquo;m going to call this project Bayley, an amalgamation of &amp;ldquo;Bitcoin&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Cayley&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migration to Ghost</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/migration-to-ghost/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2015 15:24:24 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/migration-to-ghost/</guid>
      <description>Hello, this is kind of a big deal. What is the big deal? Well this blog!
At first I thought it wasn&amp;rsquo;t that special. I mean all I was really doing was dumping photos with some captions so that my family can see what I&amp;rsquo;ve been up to on my vacations. The cool thing was that I have been semi consistent and now the blog is decently sized, with 130 posts and 1GB of (possible mostly superfluous) photos.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>