<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nii&#39;s Travel Blog</title>
    <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Nii&#39;s Travel Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://travel.niiteki.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Jimbaran 2</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2017/jimbaran2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2017/jimbaran2/</guid>
      <description>Our trusty host, Made, helped us get the scooter back.
He also makes us breakfast!
I rode on the back of his scooter and he took me to the Ayana Rimba Resort. I was worried that we&amp;rsquo;d get lost again, and guess what? We got lost! No problem though, more friendly villager types helped us out and we managed to get my scooter.
We grabbed some petrol on the way back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jimbaran 1</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2017/jimbaran1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2017/jimbaran1/</guid>
      <description>Simple 15 Minute Trip The accomodation here is amazing! Made is a superhost, meaning that you really can&amp;rsquo;t go wrong with this place.
We rented a scooter.
This evening we had a traditional Balinese dance at the Ayana resort, unfortunately Google Maps has failed us!
![Google Maps directions]()
Do NOT take this route, you&amp;rsquo;ll die!
It was a beaten track, muddy, rocky, tree roots everywhere and we thought we were gonna die.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seminyak 2</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2017/seminyak2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2017/seminyak2/</guid>
      <description> Migrate to Jimbaran This will be a short one! Our day:
 Wake up Pack Take taxi to Pak Malen Eat tasty suckling pig Order a third mains to share tasty suckling pig Taxi back to the double six AirBnB Taxi to Jimbaran  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seminyak 1</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2017/seminyak1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2017/seminyak1/</guid>
      <description>Seminyak Day 1 Today was migration day! We&amp;rsquo;re finally leaving Ubud and heading to Seminyak. Seminyak is allegedly the more upmarket area of Bali. Kind of like Kuta but more expensive.
We had a driver that took us all the way there.
Accomodation The AirBnB was located on DoubleSix street, one of the main streets heading into the Double Six Beach.
It was actually pretty nice, except for the fact that the internet didn&amp;rsquo;t work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubud 5</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2017/ubud5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2017/ubud5/</guid>
      <description>Being a tourist Today was the day we decided to do all the touristy stuff.
Goa Gajah Also known as the elephant cave. Its a half buddhist half hindi temple. Wasn&amp;rsquo;t that interesting honestly. Also my legs were absolutely killing me so I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to walk anymore stairs than I have to.
Lunch at Bebek Tempi Sewak (?) I had bebek betutu here for the first time. It is a tasty smoked duck, something to do with leaves and Balinese herbs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubud 4</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2017/elephants/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2017 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2017/elephants/</guid>
      <description>Oliphaunts Today was the Elephant Safari Tour!
Unfortunately we had to get up at 5:45am, which was kind of ridiculous. Anyway the driver picked us up in a 12 seater bus. Its actually pretty amazing how he navigated the squishy roads of Ubud with such a huge vehicle.
We were hooning up and downhill, and around windy roads for an hour or so (I think we were almost drifting at some point) until we got to our destination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubud 3</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2017/ubud3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2017/ubud3/</guid>
      <description>Raftin&amp;rsquo; Our host was kind enough to prepare breakfast for us before we left. Today is the day we will go white water rafting.
The driver picked us up at 8:30am to go to Payung White Water Rafting. His name was Dhono and he was actually a really cool guy. We got his business card to share with people who might be in the area in the future.
Unfortunately right at the beginning we had to walk down 500 steps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubud 2</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2017/ubud2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2017/ubud2/</guid>
      <description>We were actually meant to have a cooking class today. We had to cancel it because we were tired and they changed the original time from afternoon to morning! So today will end up being a day of general exploration.
Our host provides breakfast which was really nice. Just omelettes and fruits. But still tasty.
We went to the exchange to get some money out. Turns out Australian dollar is doing really well (or IDR is not) so the rates are pretty good these days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubud 1</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2017/ubud1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2017 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2017/ubud1/</guid>
      <description>Ubud So we are finally in Bali. We haven&amp;rsquo;t been here for years! This time around we intentionally avoided the more busy tourist-y areas such as Kuta.
We ended up going to Ubud instead (among others)
The Flight After a horrible Uber ride later, we find out at the airport that Tiger Air is grounded for all flights to Indonesia. Not really a problem for us as we&amp;rsquo;re in Jetstar, except all the Tiger Air passengers have changed to Jetstar!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perth</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/perth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2016 20:40:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/perth/</guid>
      <description>And so ends our long loooong trek back.
Kudos to Steph for driving for what I think was 5 hours in total today!
We left Kalbarri in the morning and went to &amp;ldquo;Barbara&amp;rsquo;s Bake House&amp;rdquo;, which was someone&amp;rsquo;s house with a van that drives around delivering pastries! Turns out they started their first day off in three weeks today. So no pastries for us :(
We continued onward to Perth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kalbarri</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/kalbarri/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2016 20:40:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/kalbarri/</guid>
      <description>We got up super early today, at 730am. This was so we actually see the dolphins this time around.
Steph thinks it was lame, because it was really windy and cold, it was raining, and the dolphins their sweet time to say hello.
We also didn&amp;rsquo;t get a chance to feed them! The volunteer yesterday gave us a tip to wear &amp;ldquo;outlandish clothing&amp;rdquo; so that we are distinct enough so that we get chosen during the feeding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monkey Mia Second Day</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/monkeymia2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2016 20:40:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/monkeymia2/</guid>
      <description>So this is the second day at Monkey Mia.
We actually didn&amp;rsquo;t do anything noteworthy.
Our itinerary for today.
 Sleep in Watch some TV (Zootopia!) Buy some water (we&amp;rsquo;ve had to ration our water since last night because we ran out) See what the dolphins were up to (we missed them!) Eat some instant noodles (with an egg of course) Watch some K-Drama (W is SO good) Nap Write this blogpost while sitting on a bench outside  So far so good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monkey Mia First Day</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/monkeymia1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2016 20:40:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/monkeymia1/</guid>
      <description>Today is the first day of major MAJOR driving.
We gotta make it all the way back to Perth somehow! So we decided to stop at different points, but this includes a little bit more driving. A &amp;lsquo;little&amp;rsquo; to some people might be 1.5 hours extra or so, but like a friend of mine said, when you&amp;rsquo;ve driven all the way to Exmouth, an extra 1.5 hours in the car can feel really, really long indeed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coral bay</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/coral-bay/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 20:40:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/coral-bay/</guid>
      <description>So today is the most vigorous and adventurous thing we&amp;rsquo;ve done together since ever!
The Driving of Car We drove down from Exmouth in the morning. It was around 1 hour 45 minutes.
The Explorer of Sub Sea We were too early to check into the hostel so we went straight to the tour that we booked earlier. Its called Sub Sea Explorer and it involves snorkelling and a glass bottomed boat!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exmouth Second Day</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/exmouth2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2016 20:40:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/exmouth2/</guid>
      <description>So today was the first tour of the trip. We were looking forward to it, mostly because we travelled three days to get to this point!
We got picked up late from the bus stop at 11am instead of 1030am. Got a tour around Exmouth and learnt about the history of the area.
Here we have the lookout point of a now defunct lighthouse.
We went for a swim at Osprey Bay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exmouth</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/exmouth/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 20:40:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/exmouth/</guid>
      <description>Oh god we&amp;rsquo;re finally here!
I can&amp;rsquo;t believe we made it!
Departure We went to Bubinga Island in Carnarvon. Apparently its an island, but the river between is completely gone now. Sooo is it still an island? Who knows&amp;hellip;
Okay fine there was a little bit of water
We ate food on Bubinga Island-thing. Standard tasty cafe food.
There&amp;rsquo;s a water tower lookout that I went up.
Much civilisation!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carnarvon</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/carnarvon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2016 18:57:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/carnarvon/</guid>
      <description>So we continued on our extremely long journey to Exmouth.
Today we went to Carnarvon. I say &amp;lsquo;went&amp;rsquo;, but it was more of a long, arduous, challenging trek.
Yet here we are!
Oh god water! Oh wait that&amp;rsquo;s just a mirage
HELLO CIVILISATION! Me trying to take a selfie while Steph is constantly being eaten by flies
We stopped by the Billabong Roadhouse halfway. Steph drove the first half (good jerb!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geraldton</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/geraldton/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2016 18:57:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/geraldton/</guid>
      <description>For some mysterious reason we decided to drive all the way to Exmouth. The place is allegedly great for snorkelling, swimming, beach activities among other things that we never ever do or have interest in.
Yanchep Starting from Currambine the night before, we drove to Yanchep to get some tasty foods.
We visited Yanchep National park. We missed out on the last two tickets for the Crystal Caves guided tour so we visited the super short collapsed cave walk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sydney</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/sydney/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/sydney/</guid>
      <description>Sydney This is probably the third time I&amp;rsquo;ve been in Sydney. I&amp;rsquo;m only here for a few days but my thoughts on Sydney are usually pretty negative. Lucky this time I have a guide in the form of friends! Vic, Alas, Russ helped me around this massive city.
Fishburners A startup space recommended by a friend of mine back in Perth. Its the only space that directly supports startups only, and does not accept small businesses or consultants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Albany</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/albany/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2016 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2016/albany/</guid>
      <description>Albany For some mysterious reason we decided to go to Albany this long weekend. It was a short holiday I suppose, and it was too expensive to go and fly somewhere for such a short period of time. Plus I haven&amp;rsquo;t been to Albany!
The trip Non-stop it would be a 4.5 hour drive to Albany. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t SOUND horrific. But in the last couple of hours you start to derp really hard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barcelona</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/barcelona/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2016 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/barcelona/</guid>
      <description>So here we are!
This is the last stop before heading back to Perth. We were in Barcelona for a few days (maybe four?).
Travel fatigue? In the fourth week of travel, we were getting pretty homesick. Either that or just too lazy to go anywhere. You can see this when we were very productive in Switzerland (our first stop), where we would move locations every day or two, do all sorts of stuff, explore the cities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>London</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/london/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2016 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/london/</guid>
      <description>London I don&amp;rsquo;t even know why there are still phoneboxes around.
We&amp;rsquo;re in London! We took the train to London from Paris! It took about 2.5 hours and we were terribly squished in the cabin. Not to mention people took our overhead storage space. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t very comfortable.
Holy crap look at that thing.
I don&amp;rsquo;t even know what building this is.
We stayed in Shoreditch, which was (allegedly) a really dodgy area but has been improved since.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paris</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/paris/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2016 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/paris/</guid>
      <description>Paris! We&amp;rsquo;re in Paris! This city is absolutely massive compared to Amsterdam.
Its a christmas tree graveyard!
Walking a lot, then cruisin&amp;rsquo; On the first day we spent mostly walking around a lot. We walked from the Bastille area all the way to Notre Dame, all the way to the Louvre! I&amp;rsquo;m no walker so my legs were pretty shot by the end of the day.
There were no lines in Paris.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amsterdam</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/amsterdam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2016 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/amsterdam/</guid>
      <description>Amsterdam! We&amp;rsquo;ve made it to Amsterdam! It&amp;rsquo;s the most tolerant of cities (or so I hear). Cycling friendly, and great views.
Getting bikes So apparently the Dutch are really big on their cycling friendly environment. We decided to get bikes of our own for this stay. We went to the closest bike rental but the guy didn&amp;rsquo;t speak any English! So we had to get by with common words between the two languages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Koln</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/koln/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2015 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/koln/</guid>
      <description>The idea was to stop by Koln on the way to Amsterdam as a stopover point, otherwise it&amp;rsquo;ll take way too long to get there! Good call I think, it took 4 hours to get here already. I&amp;rsquo;d rather not have to wait another 4 on the train!
Pssh.
For lunch we ate Vietnamese food. Not the most German of lunches, but I needed my fish sauce fix&amp;hellip;
German cuisine! Pho real.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Karlsruhe</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/karlsruhe/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/karlsruhe/</guid>
      <description>Karlsruhe We&amp;rsquo;ve made it to Germany! We&amp;rsquo;re in a small town called Karlsruhe.
A few years ago for her practicum, Steph made a friend who lived here.
Tea/Coffee We made it here after a 4 hour bus ride!
Cycle Tour Yesterday Steph&amp;rsquo;s friend showed us around the town. We had a look at various universities, and outdoor ice skating rink, and other things. Had dinner at a German pub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zurich</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/zurich/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2015 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/zurich/</guid>
      <description>Before we head into Germany, we have a single night in Zurich.
The idea was to come to the city during Christmas and enjoy the Christmas markets. This plan completely failed though. Because the Christmas markets actually finish the day before Christmas!
So there we were in Zurich, all excited to experience the city. But the entire city was completely dead. The Swiss are apparently quite traditional, so everyone pretty much takes Christmas off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sachseln</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/sachseln/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2015 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/sachseln/</guid>
      <description>Sachseln is a small town in the geographic centre of Switzerland. A big deal apparently! Only about 5000 people live here. There&amp;rsquo;s a big church and that&amp;rsquo;s about it really. The house we&amp;rsquo;re staying in is pretty amazing, super high tech facilities but also a traditional wooden house.
The view from the room
The house itself
Ancient latch system!
Swiss powerpoints confuse me.
This was mostly a stop between Jungraujoch and Zurich so we can get a decent rest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jungfraujoch</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/jungfraujoch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2015 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/jungfraujoch/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m in that photo, the tiny red speck.
The Top of Europe! Jungfraujoch is the tallest peak in Europe (or so I&amp;rsquo;ve been led to believe). So since we were both physically bad at hiking mountains and dealing with subzero temperatures, we thought it would be a good idea to go!
A pic from the top.
The Journey Actually getting to Jungfraujoch we very difficult and pretty much everything that could go wrong did (a common theory of mine).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gruyere</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/gruyere/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/gruyere/</guid>
      <description>Gruyere So we&amp;rsquo;ve been eating this cheese called Gruyere cheese recently. It tastes kind of like an aged cheddar. Good stuff, and around 72 bucks a kilo back at home. Steph found out that there is a place in Switzerland called Gruyere, and they make that exact cheese! So of course we had to go.
The train took a couple of hours.
This was the only available public toilet in the town.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bern</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/bern/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2015 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/bern/</guid>
      <description>Bern! We finally made it to Bern! Getting here was a lot more effort than you&amp;rsquo;d expect, mostly because of poor directions and getting hopelessly lost.
Cat Kingdom So the guy has a cat door, and random cats keep entering and leaving. I&amp;rsquo;ve seen two cats so far and I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure there are way more.
I got nothing against cats. They&amp;rsquo;re cute and fluffy animal. But my allergies certainly don&amp;rsquo;t agree!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qatar Airlines</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/qatar-airlines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2015 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/qatar-airlines/</guid>
      <description>Europe! (In 20 hours anyway) So I&amp;rsquo;m typing this while on the plane to Qatar.
Surprising that we got here on time considering we arrived late and pretty much everything that could&amp;rsquo;ve went wrong, did.
 Came late (normal) Check-in dude was really unfriendly (not normal) Check-in luggage got taken away for inspection Tax Refund Scheme took ages (AND it got rejected)  So yeah we were on the final call for boarding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Mk III Part Three - Other Stuff</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/hong-kong-mk-iii-part-three-other-stuff/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2015 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/hong-kong-mk-iii-part-three-other-stuff/</guid>
      <description>Tech stuff I love Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s airport express train&amp;rsquo;s progress bar.
One of the malls had seating areas which exist only to charge your phone. Its a great idea! Too bad my phone&amp;rsquo;s battery capacity is too big now, so these are useless to me.
Neat shops Ghibli Shop! Ghibli shops are great! The studio doesn&amp;rsquo;t make movies anymore (I think?) so its nice to see that the knick knacks are still being sold.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Mk III Part Two - Food</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/hong-kong-mk-iii-part-two-food/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2015 01:27:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/hong-kong-mk-iii-part-two-food/</guid>
      <description>This won&amp;rsquo;t be a daily blog, mostly because life in Hong Kong tends to blur into a big mush of stuff. So here are some highlights.
Food in Hong Kong! Service The workers here work at a breakneck pace, and I find myself constantly slowing everyone down. Its a lovely change from Malaysia. Here in Hong Kong, the service is bad because there are a billion people and so much to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Mk III Part One - Arrival and Accomodation</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/hong-kong-mk-iii-part-one-arrival-and-accomodation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2015 17:35:35 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/hong-kong-mk-iii-part-one-arrival-and-accomodation/</guid>
      <description>Hello again! Here we are in Hong Kong yet again. This is our third time here! I guess we never learn. Who would&amp;rsquo;ve thought that Hong Kong is not the most ideal place to relax and chill out.
Anyway might as well track our progress. When I&amp;rsquo;m 100 years old I&amp;rsquo;ll be saying wise words such as:
 Damn son, I was in Hong Kong 3 times by the time I was your age.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migration to Hugo</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/migration-to-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2015 17:51:31 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/migration-to-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Again? I know, I know, I JUST migrated over to Ghost a few months ago. But no one really reads this anyway, so I don&amp;rsquo;t think I&amp;rsquo;m offending that many people.
Hugo is a Go based static site generator. Its really damn quick, and looks pretty good too! At first I thought Ghost would&amp;rsquo;ve been a good platform to work from.
But as it turns out, even though Ghost works really well, sorting out:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>about</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2015 09:07:19 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/about/</guid>
      <description>About me I&amp;rsquo;m an ex-control systems/automation engineer. I’ve been working in the mining industry for 6 years before switching to software development.
During my engineering career I have spent about 3 years on mine sites, from Boddington to South Australia. I even spent nine months in Ghana, West Africa! A lot of my work involved switch configuration, PLC and SCADA programming, fault finding, code debugging, breakdown support and field testing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japan-Korea Day 6 - Miyajima 2</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan-korea-day-6-miyajima-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2015 23:07:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan-korea-day-6-miyajima-2/</guid>
      <description>Miyajima Day 2 Damn today was extremely hot and humid. I felt like I was having a bath, except with clothes on and while standing. The overly accommodating but creepy Minshuku owner gave us paper fans, which was probably the most useful equipment that we&amp;rsquo;ve had this entire trip.
It was nice to have a change of scenery from the city, although it was only for two days. By the end of the day, we were looking forwards to returning back to civilisation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japan-Korea Day 5 - Miyajima</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan-korea-day-5-miyajima/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2015 23:01:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan-korea-day-5-miyajima/</guid>
      <description>Miyajima Ok here we go. Itsukushima island (yes I know I just said Itsuku-island Island).
The home of the killer deer apparently. They will go through your bags and stuff. I better bring a baseball bat&amp;hellip;
Oh. Never mind.
This is all future tense of course. We&amp;rsquo;re currently on a rocket ship on rails known as the Shinkansen!
I always get a kick out of going in one. This is the first time I&amp;rsquo;ve been on the Nozomi, which is the express Shinkansen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japan-Korea Day 4 - Kobe</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan-korea-day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 21:05:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan-korea-day-4/</guid>
      <description>Homestay Masterchef Steph learnt to cook some tamagoyaki today! The host mother was happy to teach.
I think it turned out okay, it tasted good. But then again, eggs are always da best!
Those mini sausages were also very tasty! 
Kobe City Today we decided to go ahead and explore the city in Kobe. It was HOT! Not hot hot, but sticky, humid hot. We don&amp;rsquo;t know why everyone was complaining that yesterday was hot, when it was miserable, raining and cool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japan-Korea Day 3 - Himeji Castle</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan-korea-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2015 21:03:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan-korea-day-3/</guid>
      <description>First day in Kobe &amp;hellip;which didn&amp;rsquo;t actually have anything to do with Kobe 
Step 1. Find some suitable clothing It has been overcast and raining pretty much non-stop since we got here. This was never the plan really, as Steph only packed 8kg full of short shorts, tank-tops, and thin blouses. Everyone else in Himeji is walking around in jeans, jackets, raincoats and boots, so she felt really out of place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japan-Korea Day 2 - 奈良 の鹿</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan-korea-day-2-nai-liang-nolu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2015 21:02:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan-korea-day-2-nai-liang-nolu/</guid>
      <description>Deer-land! Deer everyone,
Today we went to Nara Park! Oh deer-ie me. I think I should stop with these lame puns or you, my precious reader, will decide to stop reading.
And we all know this blog needs more hits. I get like, one hit per year (hi Mum!).
I discovered an electric vehicle quick charging station!
I was scared to use this tap at the guesthouse. Who knows what each of those million dials could do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japan-Korea Day 1 - Nara</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2015 17:53:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan/</guid>
      <description>Nara! 奈良市! Big Temples and Stuff! Hello! We&amp;rsquo;ve finally landed in Japan. We&amp;rsquo;ve been to this country way too many times yet here we are! I think its because we&amp;rsquo;ve reached the point where going to Japan is just a comfortable process. We speak the language (terribly), and we can blend in (terribly)!
We took Malaysia Airlines this time to the country. The flights were cheaper and quite empty. I assume its because of the recent issues Malaysia Airlines have been having regarding keeping track of their planes, but seriously the flight was pretty good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japan and Korea!</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan-and-korea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2015 10:48:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan-and-korea/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re heading to Japan and Korea next week! Exciting. Except for the fact that it&amp;rsquo;s going to rain like crazy for the entire time we are there, only to clear up into beautiful skies as soon as we leave.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain Analytics with Cayley DB</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/blockchain-analytics-with-cayley-db/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2015 13:21:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/blockchain-analytics-with-cayley-db/</guid>
      <description>Bitcoin (and consequently, the Blockchain) have been making waves in the media over the past few years.
In this blog we will be covering the process of building relationships between blocks, transactions and addresses using Google&amp;rsquo;s Cayley DB. With this information we may be able to pinpoint important transfers of value and also build an ownership database on top of it to track high value individuals.
I&amp;rsquo;m going to call this project Bayley, an amalgamation of &amp;ldquo;Bitcoin&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Cayley&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migration to Ghost</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/migration-to-ghost/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2015 15:24:24 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/migration-to-ghost/</guid>
      <description>Hello, this is kind of a big deal. What is the big deal? Well this blog!
At first I thought it wasn&amp;rsquo;t that special. I mean all I was really doing was dumping photos with some captions so that my family can see what I&amp;rsquo;ve been up to on my vacations. The cool thing was that I have been semi consistent and now the blog is decently sized, with 130 posts and 1GB of (possible mostly superfluous) photos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tokyo 2014 Day 2</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/1840/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2014 11:45:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/1840/</guid>
      <description>Today we rode our bikes around. Tried to go to ryougoku by bike. Took ages but it was closed when we got there! Very disappointing, was looking forward to eat sumo food. Not so I can get fat(ter) or anything. Just that it’s one of those foods that people don’t know about. Maybe it tastes awful?
We then went to Shinjuku in the evening. Kabukicho had a pretty DODGY vibe to it so we didn’t stay long.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tokyo 2014 Day 1</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/tokyo-mk-3-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2014 17:40:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/tokyo-mk-3-day-1/</guid>
      <description>Aaand we are back in Japan. I suppose it was going to happen eventually.
This time around will be Tokyo, Kyoto and Osaka, but this time we will be adding Takayama to the list. Popular vacation town in the middle of the mountains somewhere. As luck would have it a volcano erupted there recently. Luckily the winds a blowing the ash in the other direction so we should be good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jeonju</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/jeonju/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2014 09:22:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/jeonju/</guid>
      <description>Jeonju! The City of Gastronomy! I’m guessing that means they have tasty food there. Lets see shall we…
This blog post covers two days in Jeonju, it was an overnight stay at a traditional style room, complete with rock hard thin mattresses, sleeping on the floor, and heatpiped flooring (amazing!)
So old yet so new (the place just recently finished with renovations actually)
This is an image of outside the room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seoul Mk2 Day 3 and 4</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/seoul-mk2-day-3-and-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2014 21:36:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/seoul-mk2-day-3-and-4/</guid>
      <description>GANGNAM STYLE! We went to Gangnam today just because we could. Big regret, didn’t know what to do, where to go. Turns out its a huge district, and the actual tourist places aren’t at Gangnam station, they’re at Gangnam district! So you have to stop at another subway stop.
Regardless we pushed on to the Kukkiwon Taekwondo Headquarters. Its like the pilgramage I didn’t plan to do.
 …Too bad it sucked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seoul MkII Day 2</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/seoul-mkii-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2014 21:27:33 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/seoul-mkii-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Woof! We tried to go to another dog cafe this time (last time was in Busan if you remember). The first attempt was very disappointing, filthy, and mostly consisted of toy dogs yapping in your face constantly. We decided to give it another go as other online blogs have promising pictures.
In the end, it was the right decision to make. Giant wolf dogs abound!
…In fact, I think we accidentally went to a wolf cafe, not a dog cafe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seoul MkII Day 1</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/seoul-mkii-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2014 21:13:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/seoul-mkii-day-1/</guid>
      <description>These last few days weren’t that particularly exciting. They mostly involved shopping, eating, learning how to cook, or just sleeping. But that’s the best kind of holiday for us. Though there was a pretty awesome place we went to the following day…
Our new hostel is in the Honggik university area which was fantastic. Young culture and stuff. Did some shopping in the neighbouring Ehwa Women’s University area. Strangely enough there were mostly women’s clothing there, of a more preppy variety.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seoul Day 3, South Korea</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/seoul-day-3-south-korea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2014 10:35:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/seoul-day-3-south-korea/</guid>
      <description>We had a late morning as we wanted to enjoy the ridiculous amount of space we had in the hotel. Went back to the hostel sheepishly to grab some stuff for the day.
Today we had tickets to the Nanta cooking show. It’s one of Korea’s biggest tourist shows apparently. I can see why, it was really good! Very amusing show.
We went to myeongdong after that and it was pretty cool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seoul Day 2, South Korea</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/seoul-day-2-south-korea/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2014 10:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/seoul-day-2-south-korea/</guid>
      <description>Master chef Nii and lowly kitchen minion StephCooking! We did some cooking classes in the morning and it was pretty good. I’m not much of a chef but at least the assistants there clean up after me so it takes out the worst part of cooking.
Morning class: 3 kinds of BBQ Afternoon class: spicy chicken stew and japchae
More spicy food! Always spicy food :(Two cooking classes in a row!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seoul Day 1, South Korea</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/seoul-day-1-south-korea/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2014 10:01:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/seoul-day-1-south-korea/</guid>
      <description>Hello again! We took the KTX to Seoul today. The bullet train is awesome! Makes you see how much further Perth has to go with regards to public transport. Actually that’s not fair, the South Korean transit system is probably world class. But it’s remarkably similar to every other subway in Asia, so I’m guessing there is one consultant somewhere who is making absolutely oodles of money selling his subway design skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Busan Day 2, South Korea</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/busan-day-2-south-korea/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2014 11:24:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/busan-day-2-south-korea/</guid>
      <description>This is our last full day in Busan. We went to the beach, aquarium and puppy cafe.
Haundae beach was recommended by a friend but I guess I forgot that neither myself nor steph care about these beach things. I think I’ve been to the beaches in Perth less than 10 times over my short life so far.
Anyway it was pretty empty and no one was actually swimming. It might have been because of the extremely cold temperatures, or maybe the Koreans hate swimming like me!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Busan Day 1, South Korea</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/busan-day-1-south-korea/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2014 11:04:22 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/busan-day-1-south-korea/</guid>
      <description>Well hello there! This is our first time in South Korea (not Best Korea). We’ve been in Busan for three days and I’m writing this as I’m on the bullet train to Seoul.
Day 1 mostly consisted of us sleeping the whole day and recovering from the plane trip. I feel like an old man sometimes.
This country is remarkably similar to Taiwan and Japan. The people are much louder, and a lot worse at staying on their side of the footpath.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan Day 4</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/taiwan-day-four/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2014 00:47:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/taiwan-day-four/</guid>
      <description>Quack
Quack
Our new hostel. Pretty awesome. Outside looks horrible though so we were pretty worried at first
Steph relaxing on the new sofa. At least we get somewhere to sit this time
Reminds me Shibuya
Cool wire art
No idea what’s going on here. Beware wildlife perhaps?
Steph has been buying many cutesy socks and pants while here
Such compact! Doge approves
This dog was perfectly still and getting trimmed until another dog arrived and then they both went nuts</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan Day 3</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/taiwan-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 23:19:17 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/taiwan-day-3/</guid>
      <description>I think this thing dispenses water
Horse sized duck and me with a duck face for scale
Pro gamers are so pro they need mechanical keyboards
Elite gamer shop! Had posters of pro players too
SHIN RAMYUN SOCKS! I wanted to buy these but no men’s sizing. I guess only women eat shin ramyun noodles.
Christmas is over, yet this treebread is not yet mouldy somehow
Yay no English. We somehow bought Lemon tea instead of bubble tea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan Day 2</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/taiwan-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 11:16:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/taiwan-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Hot pot lunch/dinner. Can’t go wrong with Watami. It was great in Hong Kong too!
CALPIS ALCOHOL. My life is complete
Red bean McDonald’s apple pie. You know you’re in Asia when…
Really curious what was in here, I’ve seen a few of these around the place. Maybe some tarp and stuff?
They called this chitterlings. And there’s a Chinese dish called tempura that has nothing to do with Japanese tempura.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan Day 1</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2013/taiwan-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2013 18:40:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2013/taiwan-day-1/</guid>
      <description>Attempt #1
Finally got these sandals working
Elevators are serious business here
ABSEIL OUT OF THE WINDOW
I’m case of fire…
Longingly staring at food as usual
Mos burger! Wasn’t very tasty but at least it was rice instead of bread.
Mysterious flavour…
Not sure why they got some pour soul to draw an entire map of the surroundings…
Really cool recycling system at Mos burger! You have different compartments to get rid of paper, drinks, empty cups, trays and actual food waste too!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan day 0</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2013/taiwan-day-0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 13:49:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2013/taiwan-day-0/</guid>
      <description>We began the long long trek to Taiwan today. I’m typing this while I’m in the LCCT airport in Kuala Lumpur. The service is horrible! Even at the airport, the first person you see is super rude.
Of course you probably want to know stuff that is surprising, not standard fare for holidays.
Derp, I wrote a whole bunch of stuff but the WordPress app still sucks and I lost my work as soon as the Internet connection was a little shaky.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Singapore Mk II Day 0</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2013/singapore-mk-ii-day-0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2013 21:39:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2013/singapore-mk-ii-day-0/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone! For some mysterious reason we have decided to return to Singapore. My previous experience was pretty horrible to say the least and in general I try to avoid anything involving the words ‘sing’ or ‘pore’ after some traumatising events regarding my work, food, and travel experiences.
](/travel-blog/images/2013/10/wpid-img_20131005_133735.jpg)Managed to fit two luggages worth into one somehowRegardless here we are on the plane to Singapore. Decided to go with Tiger Airways to save money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dubai MKII Day 2 &#43; 3</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2013/dubai-mkii-day-2-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2013 05:44:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2013/dubai-mkii-day-2-3/</guid>
      <description>Behold! A COMBINED post! Mostly because I’m burning out writing so much and thinking so far back into the past, and also because Dubai this time around just wasn’t that interesting. We were busy relaxing and recuperating I think.
So read on and see what exciting shenanigans one can get up to in Dubai!
Dubai MKII Day 2 So yeah this part of the trip was mostly just winding down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dubai MKII Day 1</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2013/dubai-mkii-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2013 05:30:22 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2013/dubai-mkii-day-1/</guid>
      <description>Sadly, its time to leave the somewhat sunny springtime scenery of Europe and to return to the desolate desert depths of Dubai. Its a reculture shock!
DUBAI MKII DAY 1. The Return How bad could it be?
Grabbed some airport food before the flight. KFC actually. Man I’m gonna miss that unhealthy fried chicken =(
The KFC had this mysterious button/bench hybrid. I was tempted to press it but it might start the self destruct sequence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 4 Budapest</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2013/day-4-budapest/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2013 05:26:18 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2013/day-4-budapest/</guid>
      <description>Unfortunately we were both completely dead today. I think Steph’s legs decided to stop working so she pretty much didn’t leave the apartment all day.
DAY 4. BUDAREST As for me I was pretty wiped out too. Not TOO badly though. I went shopping a little bit and got some takeaway Hummus to eat at home. Mmm Hummus.
Super scary lift towards our apartmentWe almost busted our ass and got to the city to buy some more of that lovely lovely rose shaped ice cream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Budapest Day 3</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2013/budapest-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2013 06:07:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2013/budapest-day-3/</guid>
      <description>Big day today.
It is the day.
The day of cycling!
This was quite a point of contention actually. Mostly because Steph and I are horrible at cycling. Both unfit in our own way I guess. But I really really enjoyed cycling around in Old Japan/Kyoto and thought we’d give it a go here. Apparently Budapest is one of the more cycling friendly cities in Europe. I can’t really confirm that but I do know I have seen lots of people riding kick scooters so maybe that’s related somehow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Budapest Day 2</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2013/budapest-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2013 05:49:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2013/budapest-day-2/</guid>
      <description>We asked the hostel owners if there is room service here. The guy was kind of shocked for some reason! Gave me a funny look. We were probably the first people to ask. Funny that, the reason I was asking was because we DIDNT want room service. Also when asking for a hair dryer and what the deposit for it was (10EUR back in Vienna) the guy also gave me a funny look and said “Uhh no deposit… just make sure you return it”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Budapest Day 1</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2013/budapest-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 04:48:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2013/budapest-day-1/</guid>
      <description>Ahh Hungary, the favourite part of my trip so far. Budapest anyway. Saying I enjoyed Hungary is like saying I enjoyed my time in Yandhi, Western Australia. But not as hot.
Day 1, Boo-Da-Pesht So we took the bus to Budapest. It was three hours long and relatively uneventful. There was an awesome rest stop at a restaurant/petrol station hybrid called Marche. We had almost no time to actually eat there though so I will never know the wonderful cuisine that is Petrol Station foods in Europe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vienna Day 4</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2013/vienna-day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2013 06:40:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2013/vienna-day-4/</guid>
      <description>This was the last day in Vienna. Quite a decent stay here. I certainly enjoyed it more than Dubai. Too much walking though. A lot of people here have scooters. Motorized scooters!!! I am going to get one when I get back to Perth (in about 1000 years) and I am getting one and NO ONE CAN STOP ME.
Ahem.
Day 4, Wien. Cool icecream place! In the morning we went to Tichy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vienna Day 3</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2013/vienna-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2013 06:29:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2013/vienna-day-3/</guid>
      <description>I’m on a roll! Typing at the speed of light! Fingers tapping at the speed of sound! Tendons screeching at the speed of very fast tendons!
Day 3. Vienna. Today was mostly souvenir shopping. So expensive. The Austrians (are they Austrians or Viennese? Arnold Schwarzenegger or Waltz?) love to pimp Mozart. His face is plastered everywhere! Key rings, mugs, doors, posters, shop names, shop mascots, you name it. As annoying as that is, at least it makes it really easy to find music paraphernalia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vienna Day 2</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2013/vienna-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2013 06:25:17 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2013/vienna-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Its always difficult keeping these blog things up to date, mostly because I never have access to a decent computer, or internet access. In the case in Vienna, even if I DID have access to a computer it wouldn’t help because the keyboard layout for these are completely different to English layouts. Which makes it impossible to type on if you’re a master race touch typist like myself.
Anyway thankfully here in Budapest they use an English layout (for some mysterious reason) so I can type without interruptions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vienna Day 1</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2013/vienna-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2013 00:34:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2013/vienna-day-1/</guid>
      <description>Vienna! Europe! The land of sophistication and culture. Or something. It is a pleasant change from the harsh restrictions and controlled environment of Dubai anyway.
Also a nice change was to see couples of all ages… Making out. Seriously. I could only see so many hijabs before wanting to see a breath of fresh air that is seeing public displays of affection as soon as a I stepped off the air plane.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dubai Day 3</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2013/dubai-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 01:18:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2013/dubai-day-3/</guid>
      <description>We’re still in Dubai.
Today we attempted to go to the Jumeirah palm, which is the world’s largest artificial island.
But first we actually decided to go to the Dubai marina. This failed kind of miserably because it was completely empty. We were there about 10am which is when everything was opening but that didn’t really help because there were actually no customers there. Most of Dubai seemed to be like this, giant malls and marinas that have been sized by how much money the Emirates have, as opposed to necessity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dubai Day 2</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2013/dubai-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2013 03:16:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2013/dubai-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Day two! We’re still in Dubai.
We realised that we didn’t budget properly for our time in Dubai. So we have decided to eat like the less fortunate people… At the food court!
Also today is ski day. Yes, we decided to ski in a desert.
Weirdly enough the city tends to open at 10am, as opposed to the 9am that I’m used to. Or in the case of crazy Australia cafes, 6am.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dubai Day 1</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2013/dubai-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2013 03:07:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2013/dubai-day-1/</guid>
      <description>Hello! This is the first time I have attempted blogging from my phone. Its quite difficult but nothing I can’t handle with my mighty technological thumbs.
Anyway we are in Dubai! This is the city built on evil oil money. Oil that we keep demanding so I guess it’s partially our fault too.
So Dubai has the biggest everything. Biggest mall, biggest indoor ski resort, biggest water park, biggest artificial islands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PLC programming is exciting!</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2012/plc-programming-is-exciting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2012 14:24:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2012/plc-programming-is-exciting/</guid>
      <description>… Not really. The burgers were the highlight of the day actually. They had some pretty sweet chups too bru.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong MKII 25 July 2012</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2012/hong-kong-mkii-25-july-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2012 23:59:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2012/hong-kong-mkii-25-july-2012/</guid>
      <description>Got up at 4am. Good grief that was early.
If we were to hope for a no show for one of the KL to perth flights we would’ve had to return to the airport EVERY SINGLE DAY to take the place of the no shows. Thankfully we had this nice round trip to Bali then Perth. The staff assured us that we would not have to pay the Bali entry and exit tax, and that they will send an email to AirAsia in Bali to make sure of this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong MKII 24 July 2012</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2012/hong-kong-mkii-24-july-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2012 23:59:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2012/hong-kong-mkii-24-july-2012/</guid>
      <description>Well this was my supposed last day of my trip! Supposed… right.
](/travel-blog/images/2012/07/hong-kong-mkii-23-07-2012-10-01-27-pm.jpg)Children have priority for some reason hereSo we got up and dashed over to the airport. Very pleasant being able to use the subway/MTR system for access to the airport. The flight was delayed by three hours and I was concerned that we would not be able to catch the connecting flight from KL to Perth in time at this rate!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong MKII 23 July 2012</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2012/hong-kong-mkii-23-july-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2012 23:59:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2012/hong-kong-mkii-23-july-2012/</guid>
      <description>Well as usual my update at the end of my holiday is very late! This blog post will cover 23 July onwards. The holiday was meant to finish on the 24th of July but we eventually delayed until the 25th I think.
Anyway the typhoon was going pretty crazy around now. The typhoon signals range from 1 to 10. Level 8 is pretty much danger level! Shops would close and people would be told to go home from work etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong MKII 22 July 2012</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2012/hong-kong-mkii-22-july-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2012 23:59:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2012/hong-kong-mkii-22-july-2012/</guid>
      <description>Today we planned to head to Central, the CBD of Hong Kong.
Octopus card ran out! Topped it up for both of us. Its such a good system, this octopus card. I can use it to buy food, grocery shopping, clothes shopping, anything really. We in Perth have our Smartriders and only use it for riding smartly. What a waste of technology! Wah wah privacy wah, the Chinese people here are crammed together by the millions without any issues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong MKII 21 July 2012</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2012/hong-kong-mkii-21-july-2012-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2012 23:59:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2012/hong-kong-mkii-21-july-2012-2/</guid>
      <description>Breakfast at Tsui Wah next to our hostel. Really bad compared to the same restaurant over at the Galaxy Casino in Macau. Probably because that was at the Galaxy Casino and this time was in the Mirador Mansion slums. Maybe. Regardless, food took ages to arrive, drinks forgotten (seriously, what’s with that? I think about 5 times now service staff have forgotten to give me my drinks. Maybe people don’t order drinks or something?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong MKII 20 July 2012</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2012/hong-kong-mkii-21-july-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 23:59:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2012/hong-kong-mkii-21-july-2012/</guid>
      <description>Another quiet day in the subways Good grief that guy must bash his head against everything here Today was Causeway Bay day! Headed over to the very Chinese unsounding Din Tai Fung restaurant in an attempt to find some dim summy type of food. Ended up being a standard restaurant with a really cool wonton thingo. Can’t remember the name, Xiao Lao Bao or something? Wai Ai Kan Su Pik Chai Nees… =(</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hooray!</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2012/hooray/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2012 23:55:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2012/hooray/</guid>
      <description>Damn I FINALLY got that damn keyboard! I bought it over at the MongKok Computer Centre (MCC).
98 HKD. So around 12 AUD. I suppose its good because I can actually type on my phone without flying into a psychotic rage. Keyboard kind of sucks though.
Check it out!
ALERT: Please go back a few posts to read my overdue Macau post. Its out of order! But chronologically sound, for archival purposes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong MKII 19 July 2012</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2012/hong-kong-mkii-19-july-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2012 23:59:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2012/hong-kong-mkii-19-july-2012/</guid>
      <description>We decided to go shopping today since that’s apparently what people do in Hong Kong! Unsurprising, pretty much every single building and slum is a shopping and food hall in disguise (yes, even ChungKing mansion).
We ate a brunch first, and to do so headed to MongKok. This is a shopping district well known for bargaining, cheap clothing and shoes and stuff.
As well as other horrific things not suited for human eyes Ate at Cafe de Coral.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alive and kicking</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2012/alive-and-kicking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2012 18:56:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2012/alive-and-kicking/</guid>
      <description>Yo I’m still alive just trying to get my hands on a keyboard so I can transcribe faster.
Here’s some pics to tide you over.
Rice burger, got from mos burger Dessert from Honeymoon Dessert shop. Smelly durian. Way too many doctors. Waaay too many.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong 18 July 2012</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2012/hong-kong-18-july-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 23:59:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2012/hong-kong-18-july-2012/</guid>
      <description>Well I’m finally back in Asia’s world city! Its night time already though and not much to do.
Lifted weights to celebrate my return again Headed to Wan Chai, one or two stops away from where we’re staying. Pretty cool place, but seems to be a red light district of sorts. The Roppongi of Hong Kong. Strip clubs, prostitutes, massage parlours were everywhere. Also foreigners too, surprisingly enough.
First step was to find some nice food to eat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong MKII - Macau Day 2</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2012/hong-kong-mkii-macau-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 19:33:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2012/hong-kong-mkii-macau-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Second day in Macau. Also the last. Today was spent more sight seeing stuff such as going to temples and stuff instead of going to the casinos (though we did go to the MGM grand casino at the end).
Took a taxi to A-Ma temple. Walked around for awhile and the temple was pretty unimpressive to be honest. REALLY smokey. There were hundreds of joss sticks everywhere, to increase power maybe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Macau Day 1 - contrasting environments</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2012/macau-day-1-contrasting-environments/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 00:03:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2012/macau-day-1-contrasting-environments/</guid>
      <description>ALERT: Due to severe crappiness of my Android app, images will be uploaded in a different method. Stay tuned.
Okay we arrived in one gelatinous piece over at Macau. Them thar rocking sea boats are very unpleasant to be on.
Anyway had to find out how to get in. Didn’t realise that we needed to go through the immigration process with arrival cards and the whole shebang.
Took a taxi to the hotel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ferry to Macau</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2012/ferry-to-macau/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 13:49:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2012/ferry-to-macau/</guid>
      <description>Well we’re in Hong Kong, but I’ll update our escapades later. Nothing really interesting is happening anyway. I guess my 4 way trip to get a passport we forgot counts. We’re currently on the way to Macau by ferry which is an interesting experience, not least of which Steph suffers from severe sea sickness.
Ferry is a pretty cool experience, there are customs checkpoints and feels like a crappy airport.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong MKII Day 2 Part 1</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2012/hong-kong-mkii-day-2-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 12:01:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2012/hong-kong-mkii-day-2-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Late morning. Got up at 930am. Well I suppose it’s not that late the highly industrious Cantonese folk work 10am to 10pm for some reason.
We need to get to Macau today since that’s where our next accomodation is. Not so easy getting there. In better news, no typhoon yet! No rain either. Maybe it’s because the millions of skyscrapers make it hard for the rain to get in. Dunno.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong MKII Day 1</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2012/hong-kong-mkii-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2012 23:59:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2012/hong-kong-mkii-day-1/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone! Been trying to update this thing but have been too busy surviving the chaos that is Hong Kong (and Malaysian hospitality, more aptly named anti-hospitality). And also typing on this damned phone. I need pointy thumbs or something. I knew I should have brought along a keyboard.
First day was spent flying to Hong Kong. 6 hour flight spent sleeping (I have the uncanny ability to sleep instantly on a plane.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Melbourne 2011 Day 2</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2011/melbourne-2011-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2012 16:15:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2011/melbourne-2011-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Got up early (well 10am isn’t THAT early) to transfer to another hostel. Took the tram then train to South Yarra. We’ll be here at this hostel for a week or so. Its a lot worse than I remember. Poor service, crappy rooms, slow cleaners (one hour late waiting to check in) etc.
Went to the city to walk around but everything is closed! Luckily all the Chinese places were open.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Melbourne 2011 Day 1</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2011/melbourne-2011-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2012 16:10:21 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2011/melbourne-2011-day-1/</guid>
      <description>I’m back in Melbourne! I haven’t been here for about three years and its pretty much how I left it. The only problem is that the weather is much more annoying. Very hot. The sun burns! Hopefully we’ll have some more of Melbourne’s iconic dreary rain soon to cool things down.
Will be here for about 1.5 weeks.
Arrived here by way of Tiger Airways, which was pretty bad. Really uncomfortable seats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam Day Eleven - Wednesday - Hoi An</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2011/vietnam-day-eleven-wednesday-hoi-an/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2011 23:05:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2011/vietnam-day-eleven-wednesday-hoi-an/</guid>
      <description>Wednesday. Got up in the morning and prepared for a flight to Hoi An. Got packed and then had breakfast. Tried to rush and get some nice photos printed out for tailoring but didn’t get around to it.
Took a flight to Danang. The tour guide was brilliant. Much better than any tour guide we have had so far. Makes me annoyed at the crappy tour guiding we’ve had for the past two locations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam Day Ten - Tuesday - Nha Trang</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2011/vietnam-day-ten-tuesday-nha-trang/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2011 22:59:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2011/vietnam-day-ten-tuesday-nha-trang/</guid>
      <description>We were still tired from the night before so we slept in pretty late today. Well to be exact, we ate dinner, went back to our room then slept some more.
For lunch we were walking around the main street looking for pho. This was pretty hard because most places don’t sell it here for some mysterious reason. I suppose it is because we were in a more tourist district which results in western or multicultural food (on the cheap).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam Day Nine - Monday - Nha Trang</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2011/vietnam-day-nine-monday-nha-trang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2011 22:58:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2011/vietnam-day-nine-monday-nha-trang/</guid>
      <description>For dinner our mission was to find lobster.
Went to the bar that evening at a place called Oasis something.
Can’t remember much else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam Day Eight - Sunday - Nha Trang</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2011/vietnam-day-eight-sunday-nha-trang/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2011 22:56:35 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2011/vietnam-day-eight-sunday-nha-trang/</guid>
      <description>This morning we were picked up by the tour guide from Dalat to be driven to Nha Trang. woke up for breakfast, got packed and managed to get the waitress to cut yet anohter bunch of funky fruits. Ended up eating oranges. Vietnamese oranges have green skin!
The trip to Nha Trang took ages. It was a very windy road as well. 70 km I think. 3 hours? the original plan was to take a detour and visit some temple on the way but that trip would’ve taken SEVEN hours!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam Day Three - Saturday - Da Lat</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2011/vietnam-day-three-saturday-da-lat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2011 22:54:44 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2011/vietnam-day-three-saturday-da-lat/</guid>
      <description>Saturday
Had breakfast at the hotel. We brought a bunch of fruit that we bought from the market the day before. I managed to get waitress to cut fruit for us. Had lots of funky tropical fruit, and the best one was probably the milky apple. It tastes like custard apple in apple form!
Straight after breakfast we decided to wash our clothes. The washing was very expensive and the hotel clerks would not give us any information about the nearby laundromats (they want us to use their services instead).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos for the first week of vietnam</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2011/photos-for-the-first-week-of-vietnam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2011 17:03:26 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2011/photos-for-the-first-week-of-vietnam/</guid>
      <description> Behold! We have gone to the effort of uploading all of the recent pictures AND captioning them! Please enjoy.
Saigon Da Lat </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam Day Seven - Friday - Da Lat</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2011/vietnam-day-seven-friday-da-lat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2011 00:04:57 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2011/vietnam-day-seven-friday-da-lat/</guid>
      <description>Steph is very glad to be in Da Lat. She found Saigon to be a bit of a dirtheap (don’t blame her to be honest). She likes the weather a lot more and the fact that we are living in an actual hotel with actual hygiene standards seems to impress her as well. As a dirty Vietnamese male, I have no problems living in a hovel, but I can also understand the delights of true hospitality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam Day Six- Thursday - Da Lat</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2011/vietnam-day-six-thursday-da-lat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 23:10:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2011/vietnam-day-six-thursday-da-lat/</guid>
      <description>We had a craving for Banh Mi Thit, possibly pronounced “Bang My Tit” in colloquial Australian English. We found the place recommended to us by a friend called Nhu Lan. Tasty, but the bread isn’t airy enough! Lots of pate though, good stuff.
The taxi driver then took us to a place to change money. The staff seemed pretty slack. They didn’t even bother looking at the current exchange rates, just swapped 21 000 vietnamese dongs for a dollar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam Day Five - Wednesday - Saigon</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2011/vietnam-day-five-wednesday-saigon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2011 19:14:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2011/vietnam-day-five-wednesday-saigon/</guid>
      <description>Went to the Mekong river delta thingo where the floating markets are (near Cai Be). Took damn long to get there! 2.5 hours I think. I really liked how once we left the smog we were in a more peaceful countryside area. I loved how they actually used pushbikes (a favourite thing of mine to see after being in Japan).
Anyway the place was pretty destitute. Shacks and sheds everywhere. We bought nice bamboo hats, took a cruise to the rice paper making facility (and by facility I mean people slapping the things together), coconut candy factory (and by factory I mean people slapping the things together) and wine brewery (and by brewery I mean a big distillation system using questionable hygiene standards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam Day Four - Tuesday - Saigon</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2011/vietnam-day-four-tuesday-saigon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2011 19:12:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2011/vietnam-day-four-tuesday-saigon/</guid>
      <description>Went to the Cu Chi tunnels. Nice propagandery fun. Watched a video about how the evil americans shot women, children, ducks, chickens and cows (seriously). Also learnt about the brave Cu Chi villagers sneakily using the tunnel network and using spent munitions, bamboo spikes (these were pretty interesting in a macabre kind of way) and other sneaky tactics.
Going in the tunnel was pretty awesome. So small and apparently it has been widened for fat tourists like myself already!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam Day Three - Monday - Saigon</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2011/vietnam-day-three-monday-saigon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2011 19:10:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2011/vietnam-day-three-monday-saigon/</guid>
      <description>This is probably the best day so far and for the rest of the trip.
Went to eat breakfast at Vincom Centre. This was a little bit of a failure because for some mysterious reason the centre opens at 9am but the restaurants themselves open at 10am! That’s retarded. We were dying of hunger but we managed to convince one of the restaurants to give us a nice early meal. Food wasn’t as good as it could be though.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam Day Two - Sunday - Saigon</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2011/vietnam-day-two-sunday-saigon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2011 19:08:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2011/vietnam-day-two-sunday-saigon/</guid>
      <description>We got ripped off! Was not a very good day today. Generally our plan was to walk around and explore. steph’s walking endurance (and mine, admittedly) is quite poor, but we ended up walking 2 or so hours to district 1, which is basically the CBD. Had to walk through mud, grime, fish markets, mould and all sorts of dirty things to get to the area. Once we got there we didn’t really know where to go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam Day One - Saturday - Saigon</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2011/vietnam-day-one-saturday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2011 19:07:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2011/vietnam-day-one-saturday/</guid>
      <description>Saturday We’re in Perth! Had to get up early at 3:45am to get a taxi to the airport. Ended up not sleeping at all. Got home the night late-ish (11pm?) after Steph’s Mum’s Dinner party thing. Spent a few hours packing and stuff then setting up computer and technological riff raff for another few hours. So stayed up all night. I wasn’t feeling very sharp for the rest of the day unsurprisingly enough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rumblings afoot of the motherland</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2011/rumblings-afoot-of-the-motherland/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2011 14:05:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2011/rumblings-afoot-of-the-motherland/</guid>
      <description>I’m leaving for Vietnam tomorrow! I will attempt to document my travels reguarly this time. And hopefully I won’t run into too many crazy Vietnamese ragamuffins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Final update, way too late as usual</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2011/final-update-way-too-late-as-usual/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2011 13:40:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2011/final-update-way-too-late-as-usual/</guid>
      <description>Final update for completeness! Like usual, I’ve gotten lazy in updating my status over the past week. My last trip was the same, I didn’t bother near the end of the trip either. Apparently its because I over blogged. Short snippets of updating is probably the best way to go. Note that this will be a retroactive update, since I’m actually back in Perth now! I’m just writing this as a way of closure I suppose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 1 Singapore, Day 1 to 5 Japan</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2009/day-1-singapore-day-1-to-5-japan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2010 19:47:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2009/day-1-singapore-day-1-to-5-japan/</guid>
      <description>Finally managed to get my hands on some internet to post my update. I tried using my Kindle’s free 3g internet (!) to hook into my laptop to update the blog but no go. Need more time at home to get it working. Anyway:
Hong Kong
Checked out of the hostel. It was a relief to leave that place. The staff lady was so rude as well. We had to walk around for the whole day because our flight was in the afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tokyo!</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2010/tokyo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2010 00:04:06 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2010/tokyo/</guid>
      <description>I haven’t been updating very often as some of you may have noticed. Been pretty busy with flights and stuff. Just arrived in Tokyo today. Gonna sleep then head off to hakone tomorrow. Going to be a hectic few days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5th and 6th Day in Hong Kong</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2010/5th-and-6th-day-in-hong-kong/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2010 23:29:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2010/5th-and-6th-day-in-hong-kong/</guid>
      <description>5th Day Late update, which is usually what happens when I type too much in too short a time. I guess I’m not cut out to be a writer/blogger.
KFC! We ate rice mushroom and flava crava. Some sort of batterless chicken, which ruins the purpose of KFC, also known as Krunchy FRIED Chicken. At least there was rice. No chips are available in HK KFC, instead they have some sort of monstrous fried basketweave.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4th Day in Hongkong</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2010/4th-day-in-hongkong/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2010 23:37:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2010/4th-day-in-hongkong/</guid>
      <description>Losing motivation to write detailed accounts of each day. Will summarize.
Woke up, ate breakfast. Steph ordered continental breakfast but was crappy, egg was cooked on the outside but inside the whites and yolk were completely raw. Wanted to complain but our Chinese consists of ‘thankyou’. I ate satay beef with instant noodles! Pretty good actually. Had scrambled eggs and butter bun too.
Went to Causeway Bay again for Stephs rebonding of hair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3rd Day in Hongkong</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2010/3rd-day-in-hongkong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2010 22:46:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2010/3rd-day-in-hongkong/</guid>
      <description>Getting used to the harsh environmental conditions now. Our goals today were to visit Hongkong island and find some good dim sum, visit the top rated bakery and find the street market over east in Causeway Bay.
Skipped breakfast today to save stomach space for dim sum. We ended up eating anyway over at Central Hongkong. We found the dimsum place but it looked very high end, plus it opened at 2pm!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2nd Day in Hong Kong</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2010/2nd-day-in-hong-kong/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2010 23:23:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2010/2nd-day-in-hong-kong/</guid>
      <description>Well after pleasant sleep in the dump we were in, we switched on the TV and happened upon a programme teaching Cantonese the intracacies of the English language. Crazy stuff on TV. Entertaining though.
Steph’s mind was working again this morning too. She was a bit speechless and quiet yesterday because of the shock from seeing the place we were staying in. I think she’s been well stocked and supplied for her entire life with decent living standards and neighborhoods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1st Day in Hong Kong</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2010/1st-day-in-hong-kong/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2010 06:00:21 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2010/1st-day-in-hong-kong/</guid>
      <description>Well we’ve finally made it to the tiger of Asia. One of the four anyway, and what do you know, the tiger is the dirtiest of the bunch!
WELCOME TO CITY 17. YOU’RE SAFE HERE
Upon arrival to the airport, we hopped into the closest taxi. The taxis are colour coded, depending on how far they travel, which is a pretty neat touch. After we hopped in I want to say the taxi drove off, but it was more like BLASTED off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Malaysia stopover!</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2010/malaysia-stopover/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2010 14:44:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2010/malaysia-stopover/</guid>
      <description>Greetings! So begins my epic journey across Asia. I’m typing this from my phone at the moment so it’s not very coherent. So here’s a photo of the airport before we head off to hongkong instead of me rambling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Boddington</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2010/in-boddington/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2010 14:45:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2010/in-boddington/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been playing around with the phone for a bit more and I think its great! Only problem is the lack of good offline maps and phone reception in Boddington. I can’t setup my international roaming or data packs in preparation for the trip :(. I’ll have to try and do it over the phone tomorrow while I’m at work… or maybe it’s time to just bite the bullet and agree to bring the laptop!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2nd day with phone</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2010/2nd-day-with-phone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2010 00:13:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2010/2nd-day-with-phone/</guid>
      <description>Well I’ve used this HTC desire hd for two days now and I’ve been really impressed! Got rid of the swype/slideit keyboard though because it was a lot slower because you have to move your finger so much! I can almost touchy the landscape keyboard here without too many issues. About 20wpm though :/. I’ve also just finished downloading a new software keyboard for my phone! It’s called SwiftKey and it’s pretty awesome so far</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New phone!</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2010/new-phone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2010 00:04:34 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2010/new-phone/</guid>
      <description>Greetings once again! Finally got my new phone and testing slideIT, a cool way of entering text. Its little finicky though. Hope it’ll be good enough to blog with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello world!</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2010/hello-world-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2010 10:34:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2010/hello-world-2/</guid>
      <description>Greetings fellow readers (all 1 of you), I have migrated to WordPress! Its much better than Google’s Blogspot because I can upload multiple images at a time. Blogspot is inferior.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sixth Day in Indonesia</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2010/sixth-day-in-indonesia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2010 12:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2010/sixth-day-in-indonesia/</guid>
      <description>We visited the grave of Steph’s grandfather today. It involved informal prayer, followed by the burning of paper money, followed by another prayer. It was relatively short (about 1 hour) and it was in the morning.Shopping (yet again). Bought neat things though. Steph got some nice sport shoes, a top and a dress. I bought an awesome bag, a linux penguin bathroom mat, and a ‘dirty’ jacket (no idea what else to call it).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fifth Day in Indonesia</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2010/fifth-day-in-indonesia/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2010 12:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2010/fifth-day-in-indonesia/</guid>
      <description>Shopping. Batu! We went to Batu in the evening. 4 of us. Steph, myself, Valiant and their cousin.First stop was the Batu Secret Zoo (or whatever it is called).
This is a ‘zoo’, in the sense that there are wild animals on display. But these wild animals are actually all stuffed animals! At each of the displays the animals are shown in their natural habitat, doing natural habitat things. They’re not moving though and are frozen in mid frame (since they’ve been stuffed and hardened or whatever).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fourth day in Indoensia</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2010/fourth-day-in-indoensia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2010 12:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2010/fourth-day-in-indoensia/</guid>
      <description>Decided to make some fancy drink stuff. The people here make awesome ice drinks, with really nice fruits and stuff. To make it ourselves, we decided to go grocery shopping. Took a terrifying becak ride (like normal) to the supermarket and to a coconut shop. Captured a video of the trip.
I took a photo of the guys chopping up the coconut. The people there were really surprised, asking why I was taking a photo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Third day in Indonesia</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2010/third-day-in-indonesia/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2010 12:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2010/third-day-in-indonesia/</guid>
      <description>Decided to go for a facial for some reason. It’s a bit of a girly thing to do but I thought I might as well do all the things I wouldn’t normally do when I was back in Perth! It was very painful. Some facial cream stuff, massage, picking away at my acne. Tears were coming down my face from the pain! Ah well, I’m sure it made me stronger in the end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second day in Indonesia</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2010/second-day-in-indonesia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2010 12:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2010/second-day-in-indonesia/</guid>
      <description>Woke up at 930am. Went to dimsim with the oma and aunty and the others that were my age. Pretty neat place actually, most of the people eating were Chinese and most of the workers were Indonesian. It’s an interesting racial divide, especially considering the Chinese do so well even when they in the minority and do not have significant authoritative power!
The food at the dimsim place is pretty interesting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First day</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2010/first-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2010 12:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2010/first-day/</guid>
      <description>Today is the first day of my trip to Indonesia! Real Indonesia that is, not Bali, which is what most tourists go to. I had to get up at 3am so we can drive off at 4.30am. The flight itself is at 7.30am. We made it on time. We wasted a lot of time waiting in the wrong line though (Air Asia) instead of the proper one (Garuda) due to poor observation skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Melbourne 2009 MLX Part 4</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2009/181/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2009 07:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2009/181/</guid>
      <description>Monday
Went shopping today. South Yarra. Found one specific shop with a huge sale on, and so I bought only stuff from that shop. I’m going to return to it today. Hopefully I won’t turn into a walking advertisement of said shop (CM’s). But the sale can’t be beat. Rawr!
Went back to hostel for more sleep.
Met with Hang, my cousin, and her boyfried Jules for dinner. We ate at an Indian restaurant at my behest, and it was relatively good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Melbourne 2009 MLX Part 3</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2009/174/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2009 08:46:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2009/174/</guid>
      <description>Morning everyone! I’m typing this on a Monday morning. Just chilling today. I’m going to meet Hang soon.
Saturday
I arrived at the 3pm venue about 2 hours late. But the bar had closed down long ago! Luckily I managed to SMS someone and find the new location, just around the corner. It was a really nice bar. Not much space though, only enough for about 4 or 5 couples to Lindy around.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Melbourne 2009 MLX Part 2</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/day-2-complete/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2009 09:02:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/day-2-complete/</guid>
      <description>I’m alive!
Thursday
After getting a place to sleep in, I felt the lovely, lovely embrace of a bed. Quite a lot has happened in the past few days. Thursday night was the first Lindy event that I attended. It was great fun! The only problem was that there was actually zero space. Kept bumping into people. Not to mention that due to the lack of space, there wasn’t enough oxygen to go around.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Melbourne 2009 MLX Part 1</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2009/melbourne/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2009 05:31:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2009/melbourne/</guid>
      <description>Greetings fellows! You may or may not read this blog but hey, perhaps its useful 50 years down the track when I pull out my creaking Intel i7 with a pathetic 16gb of ram to show my grandchildren how WE typed things back in the day.
My train of thought is relatively meandering at the moment perhaps due to lack of sleep. I touched down in Melbourne for the Melbourne Lindyhop Exchange (MLX).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last day.</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2009/last-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2009 23:49:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2009/last-day/</guid>
      <description>Ahh I’ve finally made it home! It was quite a stressful journey back but at least I got here in one piece I suppose. I’ll offload these final photos for you all to enjoy. Sorry for not updating often enough, but it really can’t be helped if there is poor wifi. Japan was a great place to be. Tokyo is absolutely jam packed with people, but you can always find something to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Years photos</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2009/new-years-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2009 20:52:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2009/new-years-photos/</guid>
      <description>Photos from Kyoto! The most beautiful city in Japan apparently. It was quite nice, but there wasn’t that much to do. I just got back from Tokyo in the bullet train too. Very cool. Its like a plane… that never takes off. This is the hostel we stayed it. It was really creepy actually. As you can see its too clean. Much too clean. The front desk has this creepy receptionist dude who has a fake smile on all the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Osaka photos</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2009/osaka-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2009 20:15:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2009/osaka-photos/</guid>
      <description>Gotta lay off my photos sooner rather than later, or else noone will look at them after I return! These crazy no smoking signs are everywhere, and each one is different with crazy engrish. I found about 10 of them overall I think. They are very confusing, and sound like riddles.
Evangelion drink! It just happened to be apple juice unfortunately. Damn you Rei!
In Japan, you wash the public toilets!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snowboard pictures</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2009/snowboard-pictures/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2009 11:34:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2009/snowboard-pictures/</guid>
      <description>[](/travel-blog/images/2010/10/dscf0001.jpg)
Hi all, Sorry for not updating many pics lately. The internet is very poor here and its difficult to write words, let alone upload pictures with this poor system. I’ll get some videos of me stacking it later.These pics are of snowboarding last week. It was really fun, yet painful. It wasn’t that cold either, because you work out alot while snowboarding. However when you head inside the rest house to take a break you start becoming super cold as your body temperature goes down from resting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy New Year!</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2009/132/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 02:56:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2009/132/</guid>
      <description>Happy new year everyone! I just went to the Yasuka shrine here in Kyoto as well as some buddhist temples to pray for good luck. Quite interesting, and a whole heap of money wasted on trinkets, but meh. I’ll update later, I’m a little tired from cycling for hours around the city today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leaving for Kyoto</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/leaving-for-kyoto/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2008 09:56:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/leaving-for-kyoto/</guid>
      <description>Hi all,
We’re gonna be leaving for Kyoto later today. The place we’re staying at is kindof dodgy actually, its 40 minutes away from the city centre and has a curfew. Plus it looks like a giant complex of some sort. Its a youth hostel, rather than a backpackers hostel so I don’t really know what to expect. Utano Youth Hostel link. Packing up now. Seeyou soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Osaka 3</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/osaka-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2008 10:19:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/osaka-3/</guid>
      <description>Good morning! Its our last day in Osaka. We’ll be going to Tenshinsuji or something. At 2.6km, its the biggest shopping arcade in the world apparently. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Osaka 2</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/osaka-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2008 18:40:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/osaka-2/</guid>
      <description>Greetings all! Nice to have wifi at Osaka. We went out today, only 3 of us because the others were too busy sleeping. I managed to buy some clothes (!). I got a jacket thats waaay too small for me, so I’ll have to slim down when I get back from japan. I also got a sweet watch thats sortof transparent so you can see the innards. Also got some manga to practice Japanese with (Death Note, Trigun and Haruhi Suzumiya).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We made it in Osaka</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/we-made-it-in-osaka/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 22:10:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/we-made-it-in-osaka/</guid>
      <description>Ahh made it to Osaka. It was a 7 hour bus ride! The stupid driver kept accelerating and decelerating as well, so I’ve got really bad motion sickness. I really wanted to take the bullet train instead, but Alas and the others wanted to save money. On the way back to Tokyo I’ll probably take the bullet train, because that bus ride was awful.
Upon arriving, we got lost as usual.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leaving the biting cold behind me</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/leaving-the-biting-cold-behind-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2008 09:17:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/leaving-the-biting-cold-behind-me/</guid>
      <description>Hey all,
Sorry for the lack of updates. My laptop still has no wifi, and I’ll hopefully get it fixed soon. Hakuba trip is finished, snowboarding is great fun. I wish to do it again often. I’m going to leave in about 2 hours for Nagano, then taking the 7 hour bus to Osaka.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos from a few days ago</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/photos-from-a-few-days-ago/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2008 21:36:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/photos-from-a-few-days-ago/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been getting lazy uploading photos onto here, mostly because its such a poorly designed system. I’m disappointed in you Google! These photos are of our last few days in Tokyo. We went to Roppongi and Jump Festa. Roppongi was a really seedy red light district. There are lots of Nigerian hustlers on the streets (more annoying than the Mexican ones in Las Vegas actually). We went to a club called Gas Panic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snowboarding 2</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/snowboarding-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2008 20:18:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/snowboarding-2/</guid>
      <description>Completed another day of snowboarding. We were all meant to get up at 630am, but since we were all so tired from yesterday we ended up getting out of the house about 9 or 10am. Snowboarding was much more fun today, I managed to fall about 3&amp;frasl;4 as much as yesterday. I’ve also learnt to fall on different parts of my body, so by the end of the week my entire body should be manageable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snowboarding!</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/snowboarding/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2008 08:24:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/snowboarding/</guid>
      <description>Went snowboarding yesterday. Very humiliating, as I kept falling over. Also extremely painful for your wrist and tailbone. I couldn’t get up this morning becauase of how sore I was. But I am now awake and off to do it again. I should really take lessons, but I’m hoping all this youtube watching and forum reading will be enough =)
After 4 days of this stuff I should be pretty good I hope.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hakuba</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/hakuba/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2008 22:32:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/hakuba/</guid>
      <description>In Hakuba, Nagano. Skiing time. Will update more later, after I actually actually get to use the damn showers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asakusa</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/asakusa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2008 12:49:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/asakusa/</guid>
      <description>Melon bread! This stuff is really good. I’ve bought like 5 already. Its custard centre is rockmelon flavoured. The outer green bit is flavoured too!
Here are some photos of Asakusa. Its about 10 or 20 minutes walk from here. The giant senso-ji temple is here. They put raincoats on the mascots outside the building when it rains! The other day they put santa costumes on them too. Nice to know someone cares about them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Odaiba</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/odaiba/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2008 12:15:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/odaiba/</guid>
      <description>Went to Odaiba some on Tuesday. It was mostly the Museum of Innovation and Technology we wanted to check out. For the robots and cool stuff. But to our surprise, they decided to close on Tuesdays! So we decided to just head to Sega Joypolis instead. Its an indoor theme park of games and stuff. Pretty cool, but doesn’t beat a proper theme park.
Odaiba is an artificial island (similar to the one in Dubai), built by the Japanese government during the economic boom some decade or two ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Today</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/today/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2008 19:09:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/today/</guid>
      <description>Too lazy to get photos up today. Went to the senso-ji temple today. There was apparently a festival, using these badminton racquet things. Bought a DS USB charger and stylus so I can actually use my DS now! Prayed at a buddhist temple and got a fortune. It was perhaps the worst possible fortune ever. So I tied it on some stick thing so it will go away. Hope it does.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Akihabara again</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/akihabara-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2008 20:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/akihabara-again/</guid>
      <description>Ahh the life of a Japanese local. My personal space was violated! Crushed against a sea of people. Though I am quite impressed, the entire mob moves at a very very brisk pace. If this was in Australia someone in front will randomly stop and the crowd’s movement will be screwed up.
Shibuya at night! It was packed with people. All the shops were closed so I assume they were going to clubs or bars or something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japanese trains</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/japanese-trains/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2008 20:07:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/japanese-trains/</guid>
      <description>I’m really impressed with the Japanese train system. It goes absolutely EVERYWHERE! A lot of people that I know don’t even bother having cars, and just take the train everywhere. The cost is slightly higher than public transport usage in Perth, but you gotta pay for superiority.The main problem? The trains are so good, EVERYONE uses them. I took at train at peak hour to goto train at the Aunkai (an incredible martial art that requires another post on its own).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shibuya and Akihabara</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/shibuya-and-akihabara/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2008 14:04:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/shibuya-and-akihabara/</guid>
      <description>We returned to Akihabara again, since it was the most interesting place. This time, however, we split up into smaller groups. Was very fun. Got souvenirs and talked to some pre-war guy who is an ukiyo-e printer/artist now. I wanted to buy some paintings but the ones I wanted were about 1000 AUD.
Shibuya was insanely packed. We went to what is apparently the biggest crosswalk in the world! My youtube channel has some videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ginza, Aunkai, Ueno park and ueno zoo</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/ginza-aunkai-ueno-park-and-ueno-zoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2008 11:22:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/ginza-aunkai-ueno-park-and-ueno-zoo/</guid>
      <description>It hasn’t been that eventful for the past few days. Went to Ueno park and Ginza. We also went to an izakaya (Japanese bar), but we were told to go away. I’m assuming that they did not want foreigners but I’m really not sure. Interesting experience. Regardless, I managed to go to an izakaya the next night. More on that later.There are some pics of our visit to the zoo in this entry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ueno park</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/ueno-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2008 21:36:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/ueno-park/</guid>
      <description>[](/travel-blog/images/2010/10/dscf0016.jpg)
After an hour of travelling on foot, we managed to reach the Ueno Park. Pretty cool. There was a buddhist shrine there!Here are some photos I took before we left. Cold and raining today. Chilling… This was taken from the rooftop of where I’m staying. A cemetary is so close by! A wall has been erected around the cemetary to scare people walking around it I suppose.
Not only that, here is a picture of the elevator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Akihabara photos</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/akihabara-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2008 11:03:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/akihabara-photos/</guid>
      <description>These are some photos when I visited Akihabara yesterday. Gotta love the train system here. Took almost no time to get there, and I assume its the same case for everywhere else. 11am. Friends still asleep. I think I’m going to kick them out of bed next time.
Apparently this car costs a million dollars. Not bad. Too scared to take a photo any closer in case the car’s owner has ninjas protecting it or something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Awake</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/awake/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2008 10:04:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/awake/</guid>
      <description>Been up for the past 3 hours. Jet lag is kind to me. The only problem is that my friends are still asleep and I’m waiting for them to wake up. Next time I’ll just leave on my own or something.
Just went to Akihabara yesterday. Its insanely cool. There’s tech everywhere!Currently drinking this awful green tea/water mix thing. It tastes just like water, but you get a green tea aftertaste.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Morning in Japan</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2009/29/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2008 09:47:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2009/29/</guid>
      <description>First morning in Japan. Damn its freezing cold. Currently 6 degrees celsius. Went to the shops and got some cheap food for 300 yen… which normally would be cheap but ends up being about 5.5AUD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arrived in Japan</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/arrived-in-japan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2008 22:41:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/arrived-in-japan/</guid>
      <description>Just arrived in Japan after a 12 hour flight. Good first impressions of Japan so far, insanely high density population and many many many train stops. Which is good… assuming you know where you’re going.
I’m in K’s Hostel at the moment. A very good place,., but this is the first hostel I’ve been to. Its like… Living with 50 other people. A weird experience, but not unwelcome. Good hostel though, its ranked the highest in Asia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood!</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/hollywood/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2008 10:47:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/hollywood/</guid>
      <description>[](/travel-blog/images/2010/10/dscf0075.jpg)
On our last day in USA, we dropped by Hollywood. It took a lot of trouble to get there, and the public transport was pretty scary at night. Hollywood remains underwhelming, mostly because we just came from Las Vegas (the place of overwhelming stuff).[
This is the La Quinta hotel at LAX. Nice hotel, though very pricy. They use neat USB sticks as keys to open the doors.
Hollywood! This is the Kodak Theatre, some fancy place that was closed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More photos of Las Vegas (daytime)</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/more-photos-of-las-vegas-daytime/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2008 10:39:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/more-photos-of-las-vegas-daytime/</guid>
      <description>Here are some more pics I took before I left. At the Flamingo hotel there is an exotic animals area such as pheasants and Australian black swans (!). Here’s a pheasant doing its thing.
Weirdly enough, there are flamingos at the flamingo hotel. Note their genetically awesome ability to stand on one leg.
A huge sphinx thing in front of Luxor hotel (which sports an egyptian theme).
The Luxor hotel from outside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos of Las Vegas</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/photos-of-las-vegas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2008 09:07:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/photos-of-las-vegas/</guid>
      <description>[](/travel-blog/images/2010/10/dscf0049.jpg)
Photos from Las Vegas! We went to Hollywood after Las Vegas and I have to admit it was very underwhelming. I think its because I just came from a massive high class extravagant casino resort, and Hollywood was just a normal city. Las Vegas has several large buildings on the strip (a road housing all the big casinos), each with there own theme. For instance, there is the Tropicana (tropical theme), Caesar’s Palace (roman theme), Excalibur (medieval theme), Paris (french theme) etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going back</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/going-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2008 11:35:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/going-back/</guid>
      <description>Currently on the bus back to LA from Las Vegas. I have no idea how the internet works on a moving bus, but I’m assuming it is a satellite internet connection or something. Very cool bus this one… It even has power points and little tables (such as those seen in planes) in addition to the standard TV. 2 days in LA then we’re off to Japan!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anaheim, last day</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/anaheim-last-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2008 16:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/anaheim-last-day/</guid>
      <description>Cool trees! They remind me of Vice City or Miami or something. We should get those in Perth!
An American McDonalds meal. This is the BEST burger ever! It’s just a meat patty and lots and LOTS of mushrooms and mayonaisse. Just the way I like it.
California! And me with my tourist pose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disneyland part 2</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/disneyland-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2008 18:17:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/disneyland-part-2/</guid>
      <description>Just returned from Disneyland for the second day.Went to California Venture, the theme parks other half. It wasn’t as good but still had its moments. We went on almost every rollercoaster there, California Screamin’ being one of them. It was pretty cool! The sixth largest rollercoaster in the world I think. (2nd largest in the US, highest and longest upside portion in the world)
Watched the Disney show thing as well as went to the rides I couldn’t before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mornin’</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/mornin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2008 04:52:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/mornin/</guid>
      <description>Got up at 10am today. The other guys were sound asleep even at 11am. I kicked them awake and we should be heading off to sample an American McDonalds soon. We will then head to Califonia Venture, the ‘other’ Disneyland, which happens to be next door.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos in Narita airport and LA</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/photos-in-narita-airport-and-la/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2008 18:16:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/photos-in-narita-airport-and-la/</guid>
      <description>Here are some photos I took initially.
…Real men take photos AFTER they finish their food.
First impressions in Japan? Interesting bathrooms (or lavatories, as the Americans call it). Every single toilet (well all the male ones as far as I know of course) have little baby seats, so you can stare at the baby while taking a dump I suppose.
Ahh an advanced toilet. What do these instructions lead to?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disneyland photos</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/disneyland-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2008 17:54:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/disneyland-photos/</guid>
      <description>Just came back from Disneyland. Legs hurt like hell after walking… not far at all. I suppose my legs still aren’t well made for walking around. Regardless it was better than I expected!
We dropped by the 7-11 convenience store on the way there. Beer is amazingly cheap!
…And sports drinks bottles are about 2x fatter than the ones in Australia. The Americans must need a lot of hydration.
Here are some random photos from Disneyland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Boy Blue Motel</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/little-boy-blue-motel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2008 06:38:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/little-boy-blue-motel/</guid>
      <description>Just arrived at LA and the motel we’ll be staying at for the next few days. Kinda old, but livable. What’s more annoying is the fact that the XD card reader is not working. I can’t pull pictures out! I’ll have to buy a new reader or something when I return to Japan. We’ll be here for two days and then head off to Las Vegas. Most of our time here will be spent going to Disneyland and maybe Hollywood if we can afford the exorbitant taxi fares.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flight to LA</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/flight-to-la/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2008 03:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/flight-to-la/</guid>
      <description>Currently on the plane to LA. American Airlines operates somewhat differently to Qantas but is still familiar enough I suppose.
We were in Japan for about 7 hours of lounging about. Upon entry my camera was detected in the metal detector. Normally I suppose this would be okay but here the Police can’t speak any English, and silently signal and wave you where to go, or tap you on the shoulder without a word.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flight to Japan</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/flight-to-japan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2008 01:15:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/flight-to-japan/</guid>
      <description>On a plane with Victor, in the EXIT ROW!!! Quite spacy, with lots of leg room too. Hopefully for the next flight we’ll be on exit row as well, but I chose the squishy window seat instead, so I doubt I’ll get it.
Terrible night, hard to sleep. Had some red wine and scotch… on the rocks. Classy, but for someone with my nonexistent alcohol tolerance it overwhelms far too much.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First post</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/firstpp-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2008 21:37:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2008/firstpp-post/</guid>
      <description>Hello there!
This blog will hopefully chronicle my adventures into the Land of the Rising Sun, depending if I can be bothered to keep it updated. This is my first blog, so please tolerate any violations of blogging ettiquette =)
I will be in California for a week, then Tokyo, Kyoto, Hakuba and Osaka. I leave this Friday on the 28th of November at around 11pm. It’ll be a 10 hour flight to Tokyo, 7 hour rest (!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>