<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Switzerland on Nii&#39;s Travel Blog</title>
    <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/tags/switzerland/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Switzerland on Nii&#39;s Travel Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 19:25:11 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://travel.niiteki.io/tags/switzerland/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Karlsruhe</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/karlsruhe/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/karlsruhe/</guid>
      <description>Karlsruhe We&amp;rsquo;ve made it to Germany! We&amp;rsquo;re in a small town called Karlsruhe.
A few years ago for her practicum, Steph made a friend who lived here.
Tea/Coffee We made it here after a 4 hour bus ride!
Cycle Tour Yesterday Steph&amp;rsquo;s friend showed us around the town. We had a look at various universities, and outdoor ice skating rink, and other things. Had dinner at a German pub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zurich</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/zurich/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2015 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/zurich/</guid>
      <description>Before we head into Germany, we have a single night in Zurich.
The idea was to come to the city during Christmas and enjoy the Christmas markets. This plan completely failed though. Because the Christmas markets actually finish the day before Christmas!
So there we were in Zurich, all excited to experience the city. But the entire city was completely dead. The Swiss are apparently quite traditional, so everyone pretty much takes Christmas off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sachseln</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/sachseln/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2015 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/sachseln/</guid>
      <description>Sachseln is a small town in the geographic centre of Switzerland. A big deal apparently! Only about 5000 people live here. There&amp;rsquo;s a big church and that&amp;rsquo;s about it really. The house we&amp;rsquo;re staying in is pretty amazing, super high tech facilities but also a traditional wooden house.
The view from the room
The house itself
Ancient latch system!
Swiss powerpoints confuse me.
This was mostly a stop between Jungraujoch and Zurich so we can get a decent rest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jungfraujoch</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/jungfraujoch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2015 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/jungfraujoch/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m in that photo, the tiny red speck.
The Top of Europe! Jungfraujoch is the tallest peak in Europe (or so I&amp;rsquo;ve been led to believe). So since we were both physically bad at hiking mountains and dealing with subzero temperatures, we thought it would be a good idea to go!
A pic from the top.
The Journey Actually getting to Jungfraujoch we very difficult and pretty much everything that could go wrong did (a common theory of mine).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gruyere</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/gruyere/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/gruyere/</guid>
      <description>Gruyere So we&amp;rsquo;ve been eating this cheese called Gruyere cheese recently. It tastes kind of like an aged cheddar. Good stuff, and around 72 bucks a kilo back at home. Steph found out that there is a place in Switzerland called Gruyere, and they make that exact cheese! So of course we had to go.
The train took a couple of hours.
This was the only available public toilet in the town.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bern</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/bern/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2015 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/bern/</guid>
      <description>Bern! We finally made it to Bern! Getting here was a lot more effort than you&amp;rsquo;d expect, mostly because of poor directions and getting hopelessly lost.
Cat Kingdom So the guy has a cat door, and random cats keep entering and leaving. I&amp;rsquo;ve seen two cats so far and I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure there are way more.
I got nothing against cats. They&amp;rsquo;re cute and fluffy animal. But my allergies certainly don&amp;rsquo;t agree!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>