<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Indonesia on Nii&#39;s Travel Blog</title>
    <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/tags/indonesia/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Indonesia on Nii&#39;s Travel Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://travel.niiteki.io/tags/indonesia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Jimbaran 2</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2017/jimbaran2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2017/jimbaran2/</guid>
      <description>Our trusty host, Made, helped us get the scooter back.
He also makes us breakfast!
I rode on the back of his scooter and he took me to the Ayana Rimba Resort. I was worried that we&amp;rsquo;d get lost again, and guess what? We got lost! No problem though, more friendly villager types helped us out and we managed to get my scooter.
We grabbed some petrol on the way back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jimbaran 1</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2017/jimbaran1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2017/jimbaran1/</guid>
      <description>Simple 15 Minute Trip The accomodation here is amazing! Made is a superhost, meaning that you really can&amp;rsquo;t go wrong with this place.
We rented a scooter.
This evening we had a traditional Balinese dance at the Ayana resort, unfortunately Google Maps has failed us!
![Google Maps directions]()
Do NOT take this route, you&amp;rsquo;ll die!
It was a beaten track, muddy, rocky, tree roots everywhere and we thought we were gonna die.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seminyak 2</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2017/seminyak2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2017/seminyak2/</guid>
      <description> Migrate to Jimbaran This will be a short one! Our day:
 Wake up Pack Take taxi to Pak Malen Eat tasty suckling pig Order a third mains to share tasty suckling pig Taxi back to the double six AirBnB Taxi to Jimbaran  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seminyak 1</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2017/seminyak1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2017/seminyak1/</guid>
      <description>Seminyak Day 1 Today was migration day! We&amp;rsquo;re finally leaving Ubud and heading to Seminyak. Seminyak is allegedly the more upmarket area of Bali. Kind of like Kuta but more expensive.
We had a driver that took us all the way there.
Accomodation The AirBnB was located on DoubleSix street, one of the main streets heading into the Double Six Beach.
It was actually pretty nice, except for the fact that the internet didn&amp;rsquo;t work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubud 5</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2017/ubud5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2017/ubud5/</guid>
      <description>Being a tourist Today was the day we decided to do all the touristy stuff.
Goa Gajah Also known as the elephant cave. Its a half buddhist half hindi temple. Wasn&amp;rsquo;t that interesting honestly. Also my legs were absolutely killing me so I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to walk anymore stairs than I have to.
Lunch at Bebek Tempi Sewak (?) I had bebek betutu here for the first time. It is a tasty smoked duck, something to do with leaves and Balinese herbs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubud 4</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2017/elephants/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2017 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2017/elephants/</guid>
      <description>Oliphaunts Today was the Elephant Safari Tour!
Unfortunately we had to get up at 5:45am, which was kind of ridiculous. Anyway the driver picked us up in a 12 seater bus. Its actually pretty amazing how he navigated the squishy roads of Ubud with such a huge vehicle.
We were hooning up and downhill, and around windy roads for an hour or so (I think we were almost drifting at some point) until we got to our destination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubud 3</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2017/ubud3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2017/ubud3/</guid>
      <description>Raftin&amp;rsquo; Our host was kind enough to prepare breakfast for us before we left. Today is the day we will go white water rafting.
The driver picked us up at 8:30am to go to Payung White Water Rafting. His name was Dhono and he was actually a really cool guy. We got his business card to share with people who might be in the area in the future.
Unfortunately right at the beginning we had to walk down 500 steps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubud 2</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2017/ubud2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2017/ubud2/</guid>
      <description>We were actually meant to have a cooking class today. We had to cancel it because we were tired and they changed the original time from afternoon to morning! So today will end up being a day of general exploration.
Our host provides breakfast which was really nice. Just omelettes and fruits. But still tasty.
We went to the exchange to get some money out. Turns out Australian dollar is doing really well (or IDR is not) so the rates are pretty good these days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubud 1</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2017/ubud1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2017 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2017/ubud1/</guid>
      <description>Ubud So we are finally in Bali. We haven&amp;rsquo;t been here for years! This time around we intentionally avoided the more busy tourist-y areas such as Kuta.
We ended up going to Ubud instead (among others)
The Flight After a horrible Uber ride later, we find out at the airport that Tiger Air is grounded for all flights to Indonesia. Not really a problem for us as we&amp;rsquo;re in Jetstar, except all the Tiger Air passengers have changed to Jetstar!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>