<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Asia on Nii&#39;s Travel Blog</title>
    <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/tags/asia/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Asia on Nii&#39;s Travel Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://travel.niiteki.io/tags/asia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Singapore!</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2017/singapore2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2017/singapore2017/</guid>
      <description>I feel guilty.
Singapore trip finished last week! I&amp;rsquo;ve been too lazy to actually document my travels this time around.
I really didn&amp;rsquo;t enjoy my last trip to Singapore. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t even find a decent blog post on it! Either that it got deleted during my various migrations to different blogging platforms.
Nothing has changed unfortunately, I&amp;rsquo;ll be shoving my blog post into a single one again, mostly for future reference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Mk III Part Three - Other Stuff</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/hong-kong-mk-iii-part-three-other-stuff/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2015 19:25:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/hong-kong-mk-iii-part-three-other-stuff/</guid>
      <description>Tech stuff I love Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s airport express train&amp;rsquo;s progress bar.
One of the malls had seating areas which exist only to charge your phone. Its a great idea! Too bad my phone&amp;rsquo;s battery capacity is too big now, so these are useless to me.
Neat shops Ghibli Shop! Ghibli shops are great! The studio doesn&amp;rsquo;t make movies anymore (I think?) so its nice to see that the knick knacks are still being sold.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Mk III Part Two - Food</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/hong-kong-mk-iii-part-two-food/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2015 01:27:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/hong-kong-mk-iii-part-two-food/</guid>
      <description>This won&amp;rsquo;t be a daily blog, mostly because life in Hong Kong tends to blur into a big mush of stuff. So here are some highlights.
Food in Hong Kong! Service The workers here work at a breakneck pace, and I find myself constantly slowing everyone down. Its a lovely change from Malaysia. Here in Hong Kong, the service is bad because there are a billion people and so much to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Mk III Part One - Arrival and Accomodation</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/hong-kong-mk-iii-part-one-arrival-and-accomodation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2015 17:35:35 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/hong-kong-mk-iii-part-one-arrival-and-accomodation/</guid>
      <description>Hello again! Here we are in Hong Kong yet again. This is our third time here! I guess we never learn. Who would&amp;rsquo;ve thought that Hong Kong is not the most ideal place to relax and chill out.
Anyway might as well track our progress. When I&amp;rsquo;m 100 years old I&amp;rsquo;ll be saying wise words such as:
 Damn son, I was in Hong Kong 3 times by the time I was your age.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japan-Korea Day 6 - Miyajima 2</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan-korea-day-6-miyajima-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2015 23:07:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan-korea-day-6-miyajima-2/</guid>
      <description>Miyajima Day 2 Damn today was extremely hot and humid. I felt like I was having a bath, except with clothes on and while standing. The overly accommodating but creepy Minshuku owner gave us paper fans, which was probably the most useful equipment that we&amp;rsquo;ve had this entire trip.
It was nice to have a change of scenery from the city, although it was only for two days. By the end of the day, we were looking forwards to returning back to civilisation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japan-Korea Day 5 - Miyajima</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan-korea-day-5-miyajima/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2015 23:01:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan-korea-day-5-miyajima/</guid>
      <description>Miyajima Ok here we go. Itsukushima island (yes I know I just said Itsuku-island Island).
The home of the killer deer apparently. They will go through your bags and stuff. I better bring a baseball bat&amp;hellip;
Oh. Never mind.
This is all future tense of course. We&amp;rsquo;re currently on a rocket ship on rails known as the Shinkansen!
I always get a kick out of going in one. This is the first time I&amp;rsquo;ve been on the Nozomi, which is the express Shinkansen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japan-Korea Day 4 - Kobe</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan-korea-day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 21:05:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan-korea-day-4/</guid>
      <description>Homestay Masterchef Steph learnt to cook some tamagoyaki today! The host mother was happy to teach.
I think it turned out okay, it tasted good. But then again, eggs are always da best!
Those mini sausages were also very tasty! 
Kobe City Today we decided to go ahead and explore the city in Kobe. It was HOT! Not hot hot, but sticky, humid hot. We don&amp;rsquo;t know why everyone was complaining that yesterday was hot, when it was miserable, raining and cool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japan-Korea Day 3 - Himeji Castle</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan-korea-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2015 21:03:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan-korea-day-3/</guid>
      <description>First day in Kobe &amp;hellip;which didn&amp;rsquo;t actually have anything to do with Kobe 
Step 1. Find some suitable clothing It has been overcast and raining pretty much non-stop since we got here. This was never the plan really, as Steph only packed 8kg full of short shorts, tank-tops, and thin blouses. Everyone else in Himeji is walking around in jeans, jackets, raincoats and boots, so she felt really out of place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japan-Korea Day 2 - 奈良 の鹿</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan-korea-day-2-nai-liang-nolu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2015 21:02:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan-korea-day-2-nai-liang-nolu/</guid>
      <description>Deer-land! Deer everyone,
Today we went to Nara Park! Oh deer-ie me. I think I should stop with these lame puns or you, my precious reader, will decide to stop reading.
And we all know this blog needs more hits. I get like, one hit per year (hi Mum!).
I discovered an electric vehicle quick charging station!
I was scared to use this tap at the guesthouse. Who knows what each of those million dials could do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japan-Korea Day 1 - Nara</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2015 17:53:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan/</guid>
      <description>Nara! 奈良市! Big Temples and Stuff! Hello! We&amp;rsquo;ve finally landed in Japan. We&amp;rsquo;ve been to this country way too many times yet here we are! I think its because we&amp;rsquo;ve reached the point where going to Japan is just a comfortable process. We speak the language (terribly), and we can blend in (terribly)!
We took Malaysia Airlines this time to the country. The flights were cheaper and quite empty. I assume its because of the recent issues Malaysia Airlines have been having regarding keeping track of their planes, but seriously the flight was pretty good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japan and Korea!</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan-and-korea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2015 10:48:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/japan-and-korea/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re heading to Japan and Korea next week! Exciting. Except for the fact that it&amp;rsquo;s going to rain like crazy for the entire time we are there, only to clear up into beautiful skies as soon as we leave.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tokyo 2014 Day 2</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/1840/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2014 11:45:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/1840/</guid>
      <description>Today we rode our bikes around. Tried to go to ryougoku by bike. Took ages but it was closed when we got there! Very disappointing, was looking forward to eat sumo food. Not so I can get fat(ter) or anything. Just that it’s one of those foods that people don’t know about. Maybe it tastes awful?
We then went to Shinjuku in the evening. Kabukicho had a pretty DODGY vibe to it so we didn’t stay long.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tokyo 2014 Day 1</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/tokyo-mk-3-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2014 17:40:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/tokyo-mk-3-day-1/</guid>
      <description>Aaand we are back in Japan. I suppose it was going to happen eventually.
This time around will be Tokyo, Kyoto and Osaka, but this time we will be adding Takayama to the list. Popular vacation town in the middle of the mountains somewhere. As luck would have it a volcano erupted there recently. Luckily the winds a blowing the ash in the other direction so we should be good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jeonju</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/jeonju/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2014 09:22:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/jeonju/</guid>
      <description>Jeonju! The City of Gastronomy! I’m guessing that means they have tasty food there. Lets see shall we…
This blog post covers two days in Jeonju, it was an overnight stay at a traditional style room, complete with rock hard thin mattresses, sleeping on the floor, and heatpiped flooring (amazing!)
So old yet so new (the place just recently finished with renovations actually)
This is an image of outside the room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seoul Mk2 Day 3 and 4</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/seoul-mk2-day-3-and-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2014 21:36:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/seoul-mk2-day-3-and-4/</guid>
      <description>GANGNAM STYLE! We went to Gangnam today just because we could. Big regret, didn’t know what to do, where to go. Turns out its a huge district, and the actual tourist places aren’t at Gangnam station, they’re at Gangnam district! So you have to stop at another subway stop.
Regardless we pushed on to the Kukkiwon Taekwondo Headquarters. Its like the pilgramage I didn’t plan to do.
 …Too bad it sucked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seoul MkII Day 2</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/seoul-mkii-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2014 21:27:33 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/seoul-mkii-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Woof! We tried to go to another dog cafe this time (last time was in Busan if you remember). The first attempt was very disappointing, filthy, and mostly consisted of toy dogs yapping in your face constantly. We decided to give it another go as other online blogs have promising pictures.
In the end, it was the right decision to make. Giant wolf dogs abound!
…In fact, I think we accidentally went to a wolf cafe, not a dog cafe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seoul MkII Day 1</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/seoul-mkii-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2014 21:13:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/seoul-mkii-day-1/</guid>
      <description>These last few days weren’t that particularly exciting. They mostly involved shopping, eating, learning how to cook, or just sleeping. But that’s the best kind of holiday for us. Though there was a pretty awesome place we went to the following day…
Our new hostel is in the Honggik university area which was fantastic. Young culture and stuff. Did some shopping in the neighbouring Ehwa Women’s University area. Strangely enough there were mostly women’s clothing there, of a more preppy variety.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seoul Day 3, South Korea</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/seoul-day-3-south-korea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2014 10:35:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/seoul-day-3-south-korea/</guid>
      <description>We had a late morning as we wanted to enjoy the ridiculous amount of space we had in the hotel. Went back to the hostel sheepishly to grab some stuff for the day.
Today we had tickets to the Nanta cooking show. It’s one of Korea’s biggest tourist shows apparently. I can see why, it was really good! Very amusing show.
We went to myeongdong after that and it was pretty cool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seoul Day 2, South Korea</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/seoul-day-2-south-korea/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2014 10:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/seoul-day-2-south-korea/</guid>
      <description>Master chef Nii and lowly kitchen minion StephCooking! We did some cooking classes in the morning and it was pretty good. I’m not much of a chef but at least the assistants there clean up after me so it takes out the worst part of cooking.
Morning class: 3 kinds of BBQ Afternoon class: spicy chicken stew and japchae
More spicy food! Always spicy food :(Two cooking classes in a row!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seoul Day 1, South Korea</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/seoul-day-1-south-korea/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2014 10:01:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/seoul-day-1-south-korea/</guid>
      <description>Hello again! We took the KTX to Seoul today. The bullet train is awesome! Makes you see how much further Perth has to go with regards to public transport. Actually that’s not fair, the South Korean transit system is probably world class. But it’s remarkably similar to every other subway in Asia, so I’m guessing there is one consultant somewhere who is making absolutely oodles of money selling his subway design skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Busan Day 2, South Korea</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/busan-day-2-south-korea/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2014 11:24:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/busan-day-2-south-korea/</guid>
      <description>This is our last full day in Busan. We went to the beach, aquarium and puppy cafe.
Haundae beach was recommended by a friend but I guess I forgot that neither myself nor steph care about these beach things. I think I’ve been to the beaches in Perth less than 10 times over my short life so far.
Anyway it was pretty empty and no one was actually swimming. It might have been because of the extremely cold temperatures, or maybe the Koreans hate swimming like me!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Busan Day 1, South Korea</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/busan-day-1-south-korea/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2014 11:04:22 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/busan-day-1-south-korea/</guid>
      <description>Well hello there! This is our first time in South Korea (not Best Korea). We’ve been in Busan for three days and I’m writing this as I’m on the bullet train to Seoul.
Day 1 mostly consisted of us sleeping the whole day and recovering from the plane trip. I feel like an old man sometimes.
This country is remarkably similar to Taiwan and Japan. The people are much louder, and a lot worse at staying on their side of the footpath.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan Day 4</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/taiwan-day-four/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2014 00:47:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/taiwan-day-four/</guid>
      <description>Quack
Quack
Our new hostel. Pretty awesome. Outside looks horrible though so we were pretty worried at first
Steph relaxing on the new sofa. At least we get somewhere to sit this time
Reminds me Shibuya
Cool wire art
No idea what’s going on here. Beware wildlife perhaps?
Steph has been buying many cutesy socks and pants while here
Such compact! Doge approves
This dog was perfectly still and getting trimmed until another dog arrived and then they both went nuts</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan Day 3</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/taiwan-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 23:19:17 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/taiwan-day-3/</guid>
      <description>I think this thing dispenses water
Horse sized duck and me with a duck face for scale
Pro gamers are so pro they need mechanical keyboards
Elite gamer shop! Had posters of pro players too
SHIN RAMYUN SOCKS! I wanted to buy these but no men’s sizing. I guess only women eat shin ramyun noodles.
Christmas is over, yet this treebread is not yet mouldy somehow
Yay no English. We somehow bought Lemon tea instead of bubble tea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan Day 2</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/taiwan-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 11:16:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/taiwan-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Hot pot lunch/dinner. Can’t go wrong with Watami. It was great in Hong Kong too!
CALPIS ALCOHOL. My life is complete
Red bean McDonald’s apple pie. You know you’re in Asia when…
Really curious what was in here, I’ve seen a few of these around the place. Maybe some tarp and stuff?
They called this chitterlings. And there’s a Chinese dish called tempura that has nothing to do with Japanese tempura.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>