<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Seoul on Nii&#39;s Travel Blog</title>
    <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/tags/seoul/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Seoul on Nii&#39;s Travel Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2014 21:36:23 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://travel.niiteki.io/tags/seoul/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Seoul Mk2 Day 3 and 4</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/seoul-mk2-day-3-and-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2014 21:36:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/seoul-mk2-day-3-and-4/</guid>
      <description>GANGNAM STYLE! We went to Gangnam today just because we could. Big regret, didn’t know what to do, where to go. Turns out its a huge district, and the actual tourist places aren’t at Gangnam station, they’re at Gangnam district! So you have to stop at another subway stop.
Regardless we pushed on to the Kukkiwon Taekwondo Headquarters. Its like the pilgramage I didn’t plan to do.
 …Too bad it sucked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seoul MkII Day 2</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/seoul-mkii-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2014 21:27:33 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/seoul-mkii-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Woof! We tried to go to another dog cafe this time (last time was in Busan if you remember). The first attempt was very disappointing, filthy, and mostly consisted of toy dogs yapping in your face constantly. We decided to give it another go as other online blogs have promising pictures.
In the end, it was the right decision to make. Giant wolf dogs abound!
…In fact, I think we accidentally went to a wolf cafe, not a dog cafe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seoul MkII Day 1</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/seoul-mkii-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2014 21:13:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2015/seoul-mkii-day-1/</guid>
      <description>These last few days weren’t that particularly exciting. They mostly involved shopping, eating, learning how to cook, or just sleeping. But that’s the best kind of holiday for us. Though there was a pretty awesome place we went to the following day…
Our new hostel is in the Honggik university area which was fantastic. Young culture and stuff. Did some shopping in the neighbouring Ehwa Women’s University area. Strangely enough there were mostly women’s clothing there, of a more preppy variety.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seoul Day 3, South Korea</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/seoul-day-3-south-korea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2014 10:35:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/seoul-day-3-south-korea/</guid>
      <description>We had a late morning as we wanted to enjoy the ridiculous amount of space we had in the hotel. Went back to the hostel sheepishly to grab some stuff for the day.
Today we had tickets to the Nanta cooking show. It’s one of Korea’s biggest tourist shows apparently. I can see why, it was really good! Very amusing show.
We went to myeongdong after that and it was pretty cool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seoul Day 2, South Korea</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/seoul-day-2-south-korea/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2014 10:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/seoul-day-2-south-korea/</guid>
      <description>Master chef Nii and lowly kitchen minion StephCooking! We did some cooking classes in the morning and it was pretty good. I’m not much of a chef but at least the assistants there clean up after me so it takes out the worst part of cooking.
Morning class: 3 kinds of BBQ Afternoon class: spicy chicken stew and japchae
More spicy food! Always spicy food :(Two cooking classes in a row!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seoul Day 1, South Korea</title>
      <link>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/seoul-day-1-south-korea/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2014 10:01:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://travel.niiteki.io/posts/2014/seoul-day-1-south-korea/</guid>
      <description>Hello again! We took the KTX to Seoul today. The bullet train is awesome! Makes you see how much further Perth has to go with regards to public transport. Actually that’s not fair, the South Korean transit system is probably world class. But it’s remarkably similar to every other subway in Asia, so I’m guessing there is one consultant somewhere who is making absolutely oodles of money selling his subway design skills.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>